kilometres but
キロメートルですが
the
の
I am
私は
able.
できる。
He is also the secretary-general of our headquarters. Let's welcome him first.
彼は私たちの本部の事務局長でもあります。まずは彼を歓迎しましょう。
Also present here are academician Li Zhenhui and several people from our hospital.
ここには学者のLi Zhenhui氏と当院の数名も出席しています。
Distinguished Research Fellows and Research Fellows
特別研究員および特別研究員
and ladies and gentlemen and students
そして紳士淑女の皆様、そして学生の皆様
Welcome to our Academia Sinica
中央研究院へようこそ
Feast of Knowledge in February
2月の知識の饗宴
The Feast of Knowledge at Academia Sinica is a popular science speech
中央研究院の知識の饗宴は人気のある科学講演です
I hope that every outstanding researcher of Academia Sinica
中央研究院の優れた研究者の皆様が、
The results of these studies have been shown in an in-depth manner
これらの研究結果は詳細に示されています
to introduce to the public
世間に紹介する
Today we are delighted to be able to invite
今日はご招待できることを嬉しく思います
Special Researcher Wu Jinglie is also our Secretary-General Wu
ウー・ジンリー特別研究員は私たちの呉事務総長でもあります
Come and talk to us all about it
ぜひ来て、それについて私たちに話してください
Let me briefly introduce Secretary-General Wu
呉事務総長を簡単に紹介します。
Secretary-General Wu is from the Longhua Department of National Taiwan University
呉事務総長は国立台湾大学龍華学部出身。
After getting a bachelor's and a master's
学士号と修士号を取得した後、
at Arkansas University School of Medicine
アーカンソー大学医学部にて
Department of Biochemistry and Molecular Biology Receives Ph.D.
生化学・分子生物学専攻が博士号を取得
that after receiving a Ph.D. in 1975
1975年に博士号を取得してから
He returned to the Institute of Zoology, Academia Sinica
彼は中央研究院動物研究所に戻りました。
which is now the cell
それが今の細胞です
Institute for Individual Biology
個体生物学研究所
research work
研究活動
Later served as Deputy Director
その後副所長を務める
So for 38 years he has been working on
38年間、彼は次のことに取り組んできました。
Basic research and applied research of aquatic biotechnology
水生バイオテクノロジーの基礎研究と応用研究
You may have seen glowfish on the seals
アザラシでグロウフィッシュを見たことがあるかもしれません
Everyone is curious, who invented the fluorescent fish
蛍光魚を発明したのは誰なのか、誰もが興味を持っています
We can ask the secretary general to talk to us later
事務局長に後で話してもらうことができます
The process of developing this fluorescent fish
この蛍光魚の開発過程
quite wonderful
とても素晴らしい
actually in this
実はこの中で
Secretary-General Wu's research
呉事務総長の研究
is a prospective fish study of Taiwan
台湾の前向き魚類研究です
There are also aquatic features
水辺の特徴もあります
Do this fish biochemistry
魚の生化学をやってみよう
Fields of Study
研究分野
In today's information, you can see
今日の情報でわかるのは、
Many innovative research results
革新的な研究成果の数々
Including the development of the muscles and liver of this zebrafish
このゼブラフィッシュの筋肉と肝臓の発達を含む
and the use of zebrafish as an animal model
動物モデルとしてのゼブラフィッシュの使用
to study the human Python and hepatitis virus
人間の Python と肝炎ウイルスを研究する
How to cause intrahepatic cholangiocarcinoma
肝内胆管がんの原因
This is a very innovative research
これは非常に革新的な研究です
what about the other
もう一方はどうですか
Innovative research includes
革新的な研究には以下が含まれます
Mechanism and Prevention of Fish Virus Infection
魚ウイルス感染のメカニズムと予防
There is also the sculpture control of muscle growth
筋肉成長の彫刻制御もあります
Research on regulation and balance
規制とバランスに関する研究
and viewing
そして閲覧
Fluorescent ornamental fish
蛍光観賞魚
There is also a turning point due to poor control of the fish
魚のコントロール不良で転機も
If you bought a glowfish today
今日グローフィッシュを購入した場合
These fluorescent fish can also give birth to the next generation
この蛍光魚は次世代を産むこともできる
This glowfish probably won't sell for a lot of money
このグローフィッシュはおそらく高額では売れないだろう
If this fluorescent fish can't give birth to the next generation
この蛍光魚が次世代を産めなかったら
Then you wait until this fluorescent fish dies
それからこの蛍光魚が死ぬまで待ちます
I have to buy another one, right?
もう一つ買わないといけないですよね？
So the unlicensed technology is very important
したがって、ライセンスされていない技術は非常に重要です
Let your industry of this fluorescent fish
この蛍光魚をあなたの業界に取り入れましょう
able to thrive
繁栄できる
So how do you make the fish unlucky?
では、どうすれば魚を不幸にすることができるのでしょうか？
This is a very deep technology
とても奥の深い技術です
We can also find out later
後から知ることもできる
Then its research results are published in the main
その後、その研究結果は主要な雑誌に掲載されます。
A total of 201 academic journals
学術誌合計201誌
He also holds 6 US patents
彼は 6 つの米国特許も取得しています
Taiwan has 9 patents
台湾は9件の特許を取得している
And there are already 8 pieces counted
そしてすでに8個数えられています
And he insisted on being in the world
そして彼は世界にいることを主張した
These famous monographs
これらの有名なモノグラフ
There are a total of 20 articles written in this chapter
この章には合計 20 の記事が書かれています
This Wu Distinguished Researcher is also
この呉特別研究員も
Our Secretary Wu
私たちの秘書ウー
As I said just now, he served as the deputy director and the director
先ほども言いましたが、副所長と所長を務めました。
that for the whole animal
それは動物全体にとって
research and infrastructure
研究とインフラストラクチャー
made a great contribution
多大な貢献をした
In addition, he also served
さらに、彼はまた、
The very important position of our central researcher is called the executive secretary of the Academic Advisory Association
私たちの中心研究者は、学術顧問協会の事務局長と呼ばれる非常に重要な役職です。
And the director of the dean's office
そして学部長室長は
It is
それは
secretary general
秘書長
that help promote the academic development of the College
大学の学術的発展を促進するのに役立つ
have important responsibilities
重要な責任がある
In addition to the service in this hospital
当院のサービスに加えて
Our Secretary-General Wu for his
私たちの呉事務総長の功績
Nationwide agribiotech push
全国的なアグリバイオテクノロジーの推進
also play an important role
も重要な役割を果たします
So he promoted the adoption of agricultural biotechnology by the painting department
そこで彼は塗装部門での農業バイオテクノロジーの導入を推進しました。
Industry Promotion Program
産業振興プログラム
in this plan
このプランでは
Hope to promote Taiwan's agricultural biotechnology industry-university cooperation
台湾の農業バイオテクノロジーの産学協力を促進したい
and industrial guidance
および産業指導
And how to authenticate and sanpinhua
そして認証方法とさんぴん花
These things are quite important
これらのことはかなり重要です
So Secretary-General Wu in 2013
2013年の呉事務総長
Awarded this Agricultural Biotechnology Contribution Award
この農業バイオテクノロジー貢献賞を受賞
It is obvious that Secretary-General Wu's promotion of Taiwan's entire agriculture
呉事務総長が台湾の農業全体を推進していることは明らかである。
play a very important role
非常に重要な役割を果たします
In addition to playing a very important role in domestic agricultural biotechnology
国内の農業バイオテクノロジーにおいて非常に重要な役割を果たしていることに加えて、
Promotion of international academic research
国際的な学術研究の推進
also play many important roles
多くの重要な役割も果たしています
including his past experience as a member of the International Committee for Scientific and Technical Information
国際科学技術情報委員会のメンバーとしての過去の経験を含む
叫MOON
叫月
and the International Council for Science
および国際科学評議会
ICSU
ICSU
and the International Union of Biological Sciences
および国際生物科学連合
Member of the Executive Committee of IUBS
IUBS執行委員会のメンバー
So it is a very important contribution
したがって、これは非常に重要な貢献です
More importantly, Taiwan International Sea was established in 2012
さらに重要なことは、台湾公海が 2012 年に設立されたことです。
Society of Deep Object Technology
ディープオブジェクト技術協会
And he is the chairman
そして彼は会長です
So no secretary can say
だから秘書は言えない
All the way to Taiwan's agricultural biotechnology
台湾の農業バイオテクノロジーへのすべて
Especially aquatic biotechnology
特に水生バイオテクノロジー
made a great contribution
多大な貢献をした
Of course someone with such a good performance
もちろんあんなに良いパフォーマンスをする人は
Must have won many academic awards
たくさんの学術賞を受賞しているはずです
including ten outstanding young people
10人の優秀な若者を含む
Of course when he was young
もちろん若い頃は
And this National Science Council Distinguished Research Award
そしてこの全米学術会議特別研究賞
And Hongjindui's
そしてホンジンドゥイさん
Distinguished Honor Award
殊勲賞
National Science Council Special Investigator
国家学術会議特別研究員
and Distinguished Special Investigators
および優秀な特別捜査官
So many awards
たくさんの賞を受賞
So if you want to hang
それで、ぶら下がりたい場合は、
The medals on my body are endless
私の体にあるメダルは無限です
what about today
今日はどうですか
very happy
とても幸せです
Wu special researcher will come to tell us
呉特別研究員がお話しに来ます
deep object technology
深物技術
and the sustainable development of deep marine resources
深海資源の持続可能な開発
Then wait a minute and everyone can listen to his speech
それからちょっと待ってください、そうすれば誰もが彼のスピーチを聞くことができます
just know
今知りました
his contribution to this
これに対する彼の貢献
and very important marine
そして非常に重要な海洋
this deep resource
この奥深いリソース
It is very important for our human health
それは私たち人間の健康にとって非常に重要です
so
それで
Today we hope that after listening to his speech,
今日、私たちは彼のスピーチを聞いた後、次のことを願っています。
be able to return home with a full load
荷物を満載して家に帰れる
And after a big meal
そして、たくさん食べた後は
have a rewarding experience other than
それ以外にやりがいのある経験がある
Gain better knowledge
より良い知識を得る
So now let's give this kind of applause
だから今はこんな拍手を贈ろう
Come welcome Master Wu Yun
ようこそウーユン先生
applause
拍手
First of all, thank you Dean Chongwu for this introduction
まず最初に、この紹介をしてくれた Dean Chongwu に感謝します。
Award-winning introduction
受賞歴のある紹介文
Distinguished guests, Mrs. Li Yan, directors
ご来賓の皆様、李燕夫人、取締役
Mr. Lee
リーさん
Dear colleagues, fellow students, hello everyone
親愛なる同僚、学生の皆さん、こんにちは。
then i am ordered today
じゃあ今日は命令されてるよ
Mr. Chen Wuyun said this, right?
陳呉雲氏がこう言っていましたね。
knowledge in Chinese
中国語の知識
Miss this popular science speech
この人気の科学スピーチを見逃してください
Can introduce my field of research
自分の研究分野を紹介できる
Then let everyone learn from this scientific research
それならみんなにこの科学的研究から学んでもらいましょう
Then it can be implemented on the popularization of this knowledge
その後、この知識の普及に基づいて実装することができます
then i today
それから私は今日
speak today
今日話す
It is one hole combining two
2つを組み合わせた1つの穴です
One is the sustainable development of marine biological resources
一つは海洋生物資源の持続可能な開発です。
If applied to the most important fields of biotechnology in the 21st century
21世紀のバイオテクノロジーの最も重要な分野に適用する場合
Let the resources of our planet's oceans
私たちの地球の海の資源を大切にしましょう
i don't stress
ストレスを感じません
Usually we speak from various human-centered subjective viewpoints
普段、私たちは人間中心のさまざまな主観的な視点から話をしています。
perpetual use
永久使用
use seems too subjective
使用は主観的すぎるように思えます
Then I think sustainable development is a harmony
持続可能な開発とは調和だと思います
and a concept of coexistence
そして共存の概念
Let our planet's resources
私たちの地球の資源を活用しましょう
especially raw resources
特に原材料
sustainable development
持続可能な発展
then we all know
それなら私たちは皆知っています
I'll watch this first
まずはこれを見てみます
Sorry
ごめん
what about our earth
私たちの地球はどうですか
actually a water polo
実は水球
right
右
That is to say, the earth
つまり地球は
largest area
最大の面積
It is also this water that covers
覆うのもこの水です
So we say Earth's
だから地球のものって言うんです
It's unique, it's in the universe
それはユニークです、それは宇宙にあります
human knowledge
人間の知識
Haven't found an environment like ours
私たちのような環境は見つかりませんでした
with plenty of water and air and sunlight
たっぷりの水と空気と太陽の光で
Enough to conceive for the creature to evolve
生物が進化するのに十分な妊娠量
So the creatures on our planet Earth
ですから、私たちの地球上の生き物たちは、
Without water, it can be said that there is no living thing
水がなければ生き物はいないと言える
aerobic bacteria without oxygen
酸素を必要としない好気性細菌
but without this oxygen
しかし、この酸素がなければ
It is absolutely impossible for any living things to exist without water.
あらゆる生き物が水なしで存在することは絶対に不可能です。
so we can all understand
私たち全員が理解できるように
The water or ocean is very important
水や海はとても大切です
So what I'm telling you today is that the ocean is
今日私が皆さんにお伝えしたいことは、海は
Not only sea water is fresh water, but it is also made of acquatic resources
海水は淡水であるだけでなく、水産資源からもできています
What we know about
私たちが知っていること
So the outline of mindfulness that I am going to tell you today
さて、今日お話しするマインドフルネスの概要は
probably under this area
おそらくこのエリアの下にある
One is that we use Taiwan to exchange our eyes for the world
一つは、台湾を利用して世界に目を向けることです。
Check out this comparison between Taiwan and the rest of the world
台湾と世界の他の地域の比較をご覧ください。
Our situation in the development of marine biotechnology
海洋バイオテクノロジーの開発状況
Compare this with ours
これを私たちのものと比較してください
so what
だから何
Because I participated in the report of the deputy dean just now
先ほど副学部長の報告に参加したので
I'm the one who's involved in our country's
我が国に関わっているのは私です
agricultural biotechnology
農業バイオテクノロジー
industry development
産業の発展
So what about our development strategy?
では、私たちの開発戦略はどうなるのでしょうか？
so let you know
だから知らせてください
So our biotech industry
つまり、私たちのバイオテクノロジー産業は、
How to develop in this area
この分野でどのように発展していくか
What about the third one?
3番目はどうでしょうか？
in my lab
私の研究室で
did some research work
いくつかの研究作業をしました
Some important points mentioned by the vice president just now
先ほど副大統領が述べた重要なポイント
and then explain it very clearly
そしてそれを非常にわかりやすく説明します
Then as a strength
あとは強みとして
Let everyone know what is marine biotechnology
海洋バイオテクノロジーとは何かをみんなに知ってもらいましょう
or biotechnology in aquaculture
または水産養殖におけるバイオテクノロジー
Then the fourth item is of course
4番目の項目はもちろん
What about the application of marine biotechnology?
海洋バイオテクノロジーの応用についてはどうですか？
Innovate with the industry
業界とともにイノベーションを起こす
this is very important
これはとても重要です
If Taiwan does not have no innovation
台湾にイノベーションがなければ
Drive the development of the industry
業界の発展を推進する
I think Taiwan may be so competitive
台湾はとても競争力があると思う
There is no way to do this in the international
国際社会ではそんなことはありえない
We can take the lead in this industry platform
私たちはこの業界プラットフォームで主導権を握ることができます
So industry innovation
つまり業界のイノベーション
If research results from academia can be translated
アカデミアの研究成果を翻訳できれば
I also want to make some introductions on this part
この部分についても少し紹介したいと思います
Then the fifth item is that we now talk about food safety
それから 5 番目の項目は、食品の安全についてお話します。
Very important
非常重要
So our food safety regulations in Taiwan
したがって、台湾の食品安全規制
After all, it is in line with international norms, especially in terms of water length
結局のところ、特に水の長さの点で国際基準に準拠しています。
where are we the same
私たちはどこが同じですか
where is our weakness
私たちの弱点はどこにあるのか
The shortcomings are what we must pursue
欠点は私たちが追求しなければならないものです
Otherwise, there is no way for our industry to be internationalized.
そうでなければ、私たちの業界が国際化されるはずがありません。
Then the last thing is to put my personal experience in the field of marine biotechnology
最後に、海洋バイオテクノロジーの分野における私の個人的な経験をお話します。
Promotion through the Society
社会を通じた推進
Then let's drive the development of Taiwan's technology
台湾の技術開発を推進しましょう
And finally the future
そしてついに未来へ
let's look at the first
最初を見てみましょう
This comparison of the development of international and Taiwan marine biotechnology
国際と台湾の海洋バイオテクノロジーの発展はこの比較です
That just mentioned that the earth is a water globe
先ほど、地球は水球であると言いました
Then the total surface of the earth is 360 million square kilometers
すると、地球の総表面は3億6000万平方キロメートルになります
71%
71%
ocean cover
海洋カバー
So of course there's this blunt bluntness that's bred in it.
もちろん、そこで育まれたぶっきらぼうなぶっきらぼうさもあります。
Calculated by the amount of protein that naturally exists on the earth
地球上に自然に存在するタンパク質の量から算出
In fact, 90% of the animal protein on the earth is
実は地球上の動物性たんぱく質の90％は
living things in the water
水の中の生き物たち
So it can be seen that the ocean is very, very important to us
このように、海は私たちにとって非常に重要であることがわかります。
no ocean can be said to be our side
どの海も我々の味方とは言えない
there is no way to survive forever
永遠に生き残る方法はない
So develop this marine industry
だからこの海洋産業を発展させてください
Not only do we get food
食べ物を手に入れるだけではなく、
We can also acquire new medicines
新しい薬も入手できます
Energy and Permeable Chemicals
エネルギーと浸透性化学物質
So often in the discussion of various technologies
さまざまなテクノロジーの議論で頻繁に
Everyone thinks that Ossisky humans need to develop further
オシスキー人類はさらに発展する必要があると誰もが考えている
Shou County because of the land
寿県は土地柄
The ocean is where we can still play
海はまだ遊べる場所です
important area
重要な領域
So is the technological revolution that thinks blue
ブルーを考える技術革命も同様です
This includes the development of technology
これにはテクノロジーの開発も含まれます
Application with industry
産業界への応用
The biggest problem facing us as human beings
私たち人類が直面する最大の問題
now everyone knows
今では誰もが知っています
Earth's population is still increasing
地球の人口は今も増加し続けています
Climate change causes, for example, the warming of the earth
気候変動は、例えば地球の温暖化を引き起こします。
There is also pollution that causes the environment in which we live
私たちが住んでいる環境を引き起こす公害もあります
getting worse
悪化
The third is the circulation of human diseases
第三に、人間の病気の循環です。
Or aging is a very important issue for everyone
あるいは、老化は誰にとっても非常に重要な問題です
Let's see in 200 years
200年後に見てみましょう
Earth's population has exceeded 6 billion
地球の人口は60億人を超えた
In 2013 and 2011, it has exceeded 7.1 billion
2013 年と 2011 年には 71 億を超えました
this is amazing
これは素晴らしいです
Nearly 900 million people in ten years
10年間で9億人近く
It is estimated that the earth's population will reach 9 billion by 2050
地球の人口は2050年までに90億人に達すると推定されている
will still go up
まだ上がります
Then here comes the problem
それではここで問題が発生します
The expandable area of ​​the earth is actually shrinking in a straight line
地球の拡張可能な面積は実際には直線的に縮小している
population has been increasing
人口は増加している
And it can be seen that this trend emerges
そして、この傾向が現れていることがわかります
Still pretty much this Stip
まだほぼこのスチップ
Although the population of our Taiwan is growing world ranking shop
人口が増えている台湾ですが、世界ランキングのお店です
But for Obole, the whole world is still...
しかし、オボレにとって、全世界はまだ...
A child is born with only one mouth
子供は口が一つしかない状態で生まれます
For a mouth to eat you have to have enough food for them to eat
口が食べるためには、彼らが食べるのに十分な量の食べ物が必要です
So the problem facing our planet
つまり、私たちの地球が直面している問題は
If the biological resources of the ocean are combined with technology
海の生物資源とテクノロジーを組み合わせたら
The development of biotechnology can solve the
バイオテクノロジーの発展で解決できる
not too long before 2050
2050 年までにそう遠くない
only 37 years
わずか37年
do a lot more
もっとたくさんのことをしてください
Still on this earth for more than 37 years
37年以上もの間、まだこの地球上にいます
what are we going to eat
何を食べますか
this is a worldwide problem
これは世界的な問題です
It's not just Taiwan's problem
台湾だけの問題ではない
So because we in Taiwan are very lucky
台湾にいる私たちはとても幸運です
We not only have mountains and land
私たちにあるのは山と土地だけではありません
It's more important for us to have the ocean, right?
私たちにとって海があることの方が大切ですよね？
So in the far sea countries of the ocean
だから遠い海の国々で
Well, besides us, Taiwan can develop agriculture
そうですね、私たち以外にも台湾は農業を発展させることができます
and industrial biotechnology
産業用バイオテクノロジー
Medicine Beyond Biotechnology
バイオテクノロジーを超えた医学
Marine Biotechnology We Are Not a Landlocked Country
海洋バイオテクノロジー 私たちは内陸国ではありません
If we were Mongolia today
もし私たちが今モンゴルだったら
Then we didn't show off our power in this area.
それから、この分野で私たちは力を誇示することはできませんでした。
Maybe we need to develop the wood industry, right?
おそらく木材産業を発展させる必要があるのではないでしょうか？
But our Taiwan ocean
しかし、私たちの台湾の海
The investment in marine biological technology has a great impact on our eleven system-based entertainment
海洋生物学技術への投資は、11 のシステムベースのエンターテイメントに大きな影響を与えます。
Such resources can be used continuously
このようなリソースは継続的に使用できます
So for us Taiwan is an ocean country
ですから、私たちにとって台湾は海洋の国です
is very important
はとても重要です
So in our government and academic research
したがって、私たちの政府と学術研究では
First we can see that
まずそれがわかります
In this marine life technology that can develop
この海洋生物の中で発展できる技術は、
Promote innovative industrial development with the basic biological blood position foundation
生物学的血液基礎基盤による革新的産業発展の推進
academic and industry
学術と産業
The need for the concept of truth is particularly prominent in Taiwan at present.
真実の概念の必要性は現在台湾で特に顕著です。
Because not only the industry needs to develop
発展する必要があるのは業界だけではないからです
create our economy
私たちの経済を創造する
It also creates job opportunities
雇用の機会も生まれます
Then let our industry be on the international stage
そして私たちの業界を国際舞台に立たせましょう
Can compete with others
他人と競争できる
At the same time our continued use of the marine environment
同時に海洋環境の継続的な利用
that is very important
それはとても重要です
Whether we can destroy our marine environment
海洋環境を破壊できるかどうか
or access to these resources
またはこれらのリソースへのアクセス
Well, because we are doing basic research
そうですね、基礎研究をしているので
Therefore, the field of flower houses should start from the basics
したがって、フラワーハウスの分野は基礎から始める必要があります
So at the base we except molecular biology
したがって、根本的には分子生物学を除外します
the flower field reproductive biological genetic
花畑生殖生物学的遺伝
Genomics Gene transfer
ゲノミクス 遺伝子導入
then wait
それから待ってください
The study of disease is very important and immune
病気の研究は非常に重要であり、免疫です
Because the control of this disease is
なぜなら、この病気をコントロールするのは、
not only important to people
人にとって大切なだけではなく
It is also necessary for these creatures
これらの生き物にも必要です
from here we can
ここからできること
not only get this food
この食べ物を手に入れるだけではなく
At the same time we can get biological active substances
同時に生理活性物質も取得できます
so in the ocean
だから海の中で
For example, we are famous in Taiwan
たとえば、私たちは台湾では有名です
We get collagen from Wu Guoyu Yilin Tablets
Wu Guoyu Yilinタブレットからコラーゲンを摂取します
then from some early years
まあ、何年か初期から
Recently, flower houses in Taiwan usually get this crane halide
最近、台湾の花屋ではこの鶴のハロゲン化物がよく使われています。
Can be used as an adjunct to chemotherapy for this cancer
このがんの化学療法の補助として使用できます
very effective product
非常に効果的な製品
Therefore, the active substances of marine organisms
したがって、海洋生物の活性物質は、
There is a lot of room for development
開発の余地はたくさんあります
then the marine environment
それから海洋環境
Sustain applications that include energy
エネルギーを含むアプリケーションの維持
including this removal of contamination
この汚染除去も含めて
biotechnology for the marine environment
海洋環境のためのバイオテクノロジー
is very important
はとても重要です
so what
だから何
This extends to the industry
これは業界にも広がります
What about Taiwan?
台湾はどうですか？
This technology of production and breeding in the past is very good
昔のこの生産・育種技術は非常に優れています
So we keep introducing new technology
そのため、私たちは新しいテクノロジーを導入し続けます
Let Taiwan's production and breeding technology
生産・育種技術は台湾におまかせ
able to continue to use
使い続けることができる
Personally, I will dig deeper in this area.
個人的にはこの分野をさらに深く掘り下げていきます。
That pair of marine naturals blossoming into medicine
医学として開花する海洋生物のペア
Flowering into new biomaterials
新しい生体材料への開花
What about materials that blossom into energy?
エネルギーを開花させる物質についてはどうでしょうか？
These are quite potential
これらはかなりの可能性を秘めています
And finally, the protection of the environment
そして最後に、環境の保護
What about resource management?
リソース管理についてはどうですか?
it's all about this
それはすべてこれについてです
In terms of application, it has considerable potential.
応用という点では、かなりの可能性を秘めています。
so let's see
それでは見てみましょう
The countries of the world these from Asia
アジアからの世界の国々
all the way to this Europe
はるばるこのヨーロッパまで
What about the countries of the world?
世界の国々はどうでしょうか？
It's in the research field of marine biotechnology
海洋バイオテクノロジーの研究分野です
it does some tidying up
それはいくつかの整理整頓をします
Discovery, such as Asian countries
アジア諸国などの発見
It says that 80% of aquaculture production is in the Asian region
養殖生産量の80％がアジア地域で行われているという。
Therefore, countries in the Asian region include Taiwan
したがって、アジア地域には台湾も含まれます。
China, India, South Korea, Japan, Southeast Asia and other countries
中国、インド、韓国、日本、東南アジア、その他の国
Aquaculture, marine biotechnology
水産養殖、海洋バイオテクノロジー
In particular, Taiwan attaches special importance to
特に台湾が重視しているのは、
Various resources including living organisms and other biofuels
生物やその他のバイオ燃料を含むさまざまな資源
Just mentioned medicine, food, feed, peanuts, etc.
先ほど、医薬品、食品、飼料、ピーナッツなどを挙げました。
are doing
やっている
The same goes for other countries
他の国も同様です
But the resources of marine organisms are different
しかし、海洋生物の資源は異なります
Fish, Shellfish, Shrimp, Microorganisms
魚類、貝類、蝦類、微生物
algae are different
藻は違うよ
so spendable features
非常に高価な機能
find new discoveries
新しい発見を見つける
Of course, each from the biological conditions
もちろん、それぞれの生物学的条件から
to find our specialties
私たちの専門分野を見つけるために
We are all very familiar with Taiwan
私たちは皆、台湾についてよく知っています
You may not know the number
番号が分からないかもしれません
The world has 440,000 kilometers of coastline
世界には44万キロメートルの海岸線がある
Taiwan's coastline is 1,600 kilometers long
台湾の海岸線は1,600キロメートルもある
About the whole world of the earth
地球全体について
One-fourth of the total length of the coastline
海岸線全長の4分の1
That's not bad, isn't it?
それは悪くないですよね？
We think Taiwan is small
私たちは台湾は小さいと思っています
Actually not small
実は小さくない
because of this
このため
Our coastline is still in the world
私たちの海岸線はまだ世界にあります
can still be listed as our length
私たちの長さとしてまだリストすることができます
The second important thing is our Taiwan
次に重要なことは私たちの台湾です
Where's this black grass from the south?
南からのこの黒い草はどこにありますか？
has two tributaries
2つの支流がある
The mainstream is from the east coast of the Pacific
主流は太平洋の東海岸からのものです
It's from Hualien and Taitung.
花蓮と台東から来ました。
Yilan keeps going up
宜蘭は上昇を続ける
What about other tributaries?
他の支流はどうですか？
from the Taiwan Strait
台湾海峡から
So what about this luck?
さて、この運はどうでしょうか？
we are very rich
私たちはとても裕福です
the resources of the ocean
海の資源
then let this this
じゃあこれをこれにしましょう
The conditions of our marine ecology are particularly good
私たちの海洋生態系の状態は特に良好です
For example, the earth is better than the earth
たとえば、地球は地球よりも優れています
Types of fish probably
魚の種類はおそらく
24,000 to 5,000 species
24,000～5,000種
already recorded
すでに録音されています
There are more than 2,300 kinds of fish in Taiwan
台湾には2,300種類以上の魚がいる
recorded
記録された
that is one tenth
それは10分の1です
Therefore, although Taiwan is small
そのため、台湾は小さいながらも、
But biological resources are very rich
しかし、生物資源は非常に豊富です
What's more, we have three hundred kinds of Sanwu
さらに、三呉は300種類あります。
The doubling of the 2,500 species
2,500種が倍増
So
それで
The next series has 340 kinds
次のシリーズは340種類
So this kind of style research is
このようなスタイルの研究は
we can play
我々は再生することができます
to make scientific discoveries
科学的な発見をするために
basis for future applications
将来のアプリケーションの基礎
Then Taiwan's production and breeding
それから台湾の生産と繁殖
Well, they are actually talking
まあ、彼らは実際に話しています
From Zheng Shenggong to Taiwan
鄭成功から台湾へ
Started to develop private equity farming in Tainan
台南でプライベートエクイティ農業の開発を開始
Isn't that very out of the ordinary?
それは非常に普通ではありませんか？
But also Taiwan's production and breeding
台湾の生産と繁殖も
Our ancestors were already very familiar with
私たちの祖先はすでによく知っていました
can only use the resources of the ocean
海の資源しか使えない
Cultivate such delicious fish
こんなに美味しい魚を養殖するなんて
So from 1661 to 1962
つまり、1661 年から 1962 年まで
you see so long
とても長く見えますね
Then it is a pastoral farming
それから牧畜です
More out of the ordinary farming and herding fish, etc.
さらに非日常的な養殖や魚の飼育など。
Then we start
それでは始めましょう
Successful technology with development above
上記の開発により成功した技術
Raising grass lotus carp and grass shrimp
草ハス魚と草エビの飼育
Artificial link of mullet
ボラの人工リンク
This technology was introduced in the 660s of the Republic of China
この技術は中華民国の660年代に導入されました。
5060s established technology
5060年代に確立されたテクノロジー
Then we started to combine technologies
それから私たちはテクノロジーを組み合わせ始めました
corporate farming
企業農業
This is Taiwan from 1970 to 1979
これは 1970 年から 1979 年の台湾です
It was the glorious era from the 1960s to the 1970s
1960年代から1970年代にかけての輝かしい時代でした
then based on this
それからこれに基づいて
So we know Manyu and Caoxia
だから私たちはマニュとカオシアを知っています
Both call Taiwan the Kingdom of Manyu
両者とも台湾を万有王国と呼ぶ
or the Grass Summer Kingdom
または草夏の王国
Grass summer is hardly cultivated now
夏草は現在ほとんど栽培されていません
It's the king carved the king
それは王が王を彫ったものです
But this is of course a sick question
しかし、これはもちろんひどい質問です
then i mean
それならつまり
I remember when I just returned home
ちょうど家に帰ったときのことを思い出します
Manyu farming is officially the most prosperous time
マニュの農業は正式に最も繁栄する時期です
At that time Taiwan
当時の台湾
At that time, when Manyu was exported, one kilogram was
当時、マニュが輸出されていたのは1キログラムでした。
about 10 dollars
約10ドル
At that time, one to four was 10 yuan
当時は1～4が10元でした
dollar one dollar
1ドル
At that time, we exported from Taiwan every year
当時は毎年台湾に輸出していました
Probably reached 1 billion US dollars
おそらく10億ドルに達するでしょう
It is Guangman language export has always been
それは常に広範語の輸出です
In just one year, the NT$40 billion at that time
わずか1年で当時の400億台湾ドル
So go to Manyu City
それでマニュシティへ行きます
those rambunctious bosses
あの乱暴な上司たち
Taipei City is still driving this era of empty talk
台北市は依然としてこの空虚な議論の時代を推進している
I have already done a lot of driving Benz and VNW
私はすでにベンツとVNWをたくさん運転しました
what about later
後はどうですか？
Grass summer cultivated
夏に栽培される草
When going to the south to go to the shrimp pond, there are also double B cars driving
エビ池に行くために南に行くとダブルBの車も走っています
So that's all the glory days
それが栄光の日々のすべてです
We can't always remember the glory
私たちは栄光をいつも覚えているわけではない
Disappeared due to illness
病気のため失踪した
So we have sick problems
それで私たちは病気の問題を抱えています
There is the problem of groundwater subsidence, etc.
地下水沈下などの問題があります。
So we are already afraid to talk about the so-called kingdom
だから私たちはいわゆる王国について話すことをすでに恐れています
But we are in this recession
しかし、私たちはこの不況の中にいます
The government still invests a lot of funds to introduce biotechnology
政府は今でもバイオテクノロジーの導入に多額の資金を投資している
Hope Taiwan can continue to lead
台湾が引き続きリードしてくれることを期待
In fact our technologies
実際、私たちのテクノロジー
Especially in mainland China or Southeast Asia, India, etc.
特に中国本土や東南アジア、インドなどでは。
I very much hope that these new biotechnologies in Taiwan that produce and raise bats
コウモリを生産し飼育するこれらの新しいバイオテクノロジーが台湾で普及することを非常に期待しています。
You can go to these countries to develop this industry
この産業を発展させるためにこれらの国に行くことができます
Here's the Science Development for Our Congressional Bloggers
議会ブロガー向けの科学開発はこちら
the analysis they did
彼らが行った分析
The resources we just talked about in the repo
リポジトリで説明したリソース
The resources of the ocean cannot be sustainable
海洋資源は持続可能ではない
Because humans overfill it, right?
人間が過剰に詰め込んでしまうからですよね？
Pollution, wait
汚染、待ってください
Then I will give two examples
それでは例を 2 つ挙げます
One is from this our
1つはこれからです。
We love to eat tuna Sashimi
私たちはマグロの刺身を食べるのが大好きです
But everyone understands
でもみんな分かってるよ
When is the highest peak in Taiwan?
台湾の最高峰はいつですか?
Where is this Sashimi?
この刺身はどこにありますか？
not tuna
マグロではありません
Can catch 10,000 tails a year
年間1万尾も獲れる
about fourteen years ago
約14年前
Now catch only five hundred and five tails
今は55尾だけを捕まえます
This resource is
このリソースは
This decline is very fast
この衰退は非常に速いです
This is our responsibility
これは私たちの責任です
So how about technology
ではテクノロジーはどうでしょうか
So in fact in some countries
実際、いくつかの国では
in australia mexico
オーストラリアでメキシコで
They have developed the only farming industry
彼らは唯一の農業産業を発展させた
We do not have such an environmental management in Taiwan
台湾にはそのような環境管理はありません
the only meaning is to say
唯一の意味は言うことです
When resources are scarce
資源が不足しているとき
Then this can only be developed by breeding
となるとこれは品種改良によってしか開発できない
The second one is that the mullet roe will grow this year
2つ目は今年はカラスミが育つということ
the price is very
価格は非常に高いです
So because we used to peak at
以前はピークだったので
At this time of the American League East?
アメリカンリーグ東地区のこの時期に？
I remember when I was a kid
子供の頃を思い出します
I'm getting better. Wow, everyone is so happy.
だいぶ良くなってきました、わあ、みんな大満足です。
Because every year Taiwan catches
台湾は毎年漁獲しているので
So that fishery technology is not very good
漁業技術があまり良くないので、
Every year, one million tails are caught, and the material benefits of two million tails
毎年、100万尾が捕獲され、200万尾の物質的利益
There's value in it, right?
そこには価値がありますよね？
Now the annual catch may be 200,000 to 300,000
現在、年間漁獲量は20万～30万尾といわれています。
So like this year, there are almost 300,000 tails
今年と同じように30万尾近くあります
So the material benefit value becomes very noble
したがって、物質的な利益の価値は非常に高貴になります
very expensive good
非常に高価で良い
Then it's resource-hungry
そうなるとリソースを大量に消費します
But Taiwan also has a place to overcome
しかし台湾にも克服すべき場所がある
It is the material benefit that Taiwan can raise a whole foot
台湾が足全体を上げられることは物質的な利益です
Raised for two to three years
2～3年育てた
The benefit value can be raised to almost a sum
給付額はほぼ総額まで引き上げられる
Can be raised to 8292
8292まで上げることができます
Quality is hardly grasped naturally
品質は自然には把握されにくい
So this technology can still overcome
つまり、このテクノロジーはまだ克服できる
this scarcity of resources
この資源の不足
So this technology in Taiwan
つまり、台湾のこの技術は
That is, aquaculture technology
つまり養殖技術
Molecular Biology
分子生物学
What's more, the development of this algae biotechnology
さらに、この藻類のバイオテクノロジーの開発により、
This is our Taiwan
ここは私たちの台湾です
more important
より重要
Can provide many of our needs
私たちのニーズの多くを提供できる
So
それで
Humans just mentioned that humans will rely on
人間が依存すると先ほど人間が言いました
this
これ
With the product as a source of food
製品を食料源として
So
それで
The adsorbed ones are usually better than the road ones
通常、吸着されたものはロードのものよりも優れています
regular chicken
普通のチキン
This pork is more expensive
この豚肉はもっと高価です
and
と
also many times more expensive
また何倍も高価です
So
それで
economic development
経済発展
The consumption of adsorption will definitely increase
吸着の消費量は確実に増える
so this
したがって、この
A statistic from the world's FAO
全世界FAO的一個統計
It was 2007
2007年のことでした
Everyone in the world eats it a year
世界中の人が毎年食べています
16.7 kg of fish
魚16.7kg
So
それで
18.6 kg in 2010
2010年 18.6kg
About 26 kg to 28 kg in Taiwan
台湾では約26kg～28kg
We in Taiwan still eat fish
台湾では今でも魚を食べます
eat more
もっと食べる
so
それで
This consumption is increased
この消費量が増加します
but
しかし
fish eaten here
ここで食べる魚
some fish
何匹かの魚
Some are from aquatic products
一部は水産物からのものです
There are two sources
ソースは2つあります
then you can tell
そうすれば言えるよ
The blue piece of the egg
卵の青い部分
yes
はい
worldwide
全世界
Doubts about compensation
補償についての疑問
so far probably because of resource management
これまでのところ、おそらくリソース管理のせいです
probably it doesn't grow much
おそらくあまり成長しないと思います
A little bit can probably replenish the amount
少しずつ量を補充できそうです
About 90 million metric tons
約9,000万トン
Doubtful
疑わしい
Then it's this piece
それではこの作品です
In the past, the amount of breeding was very small
昔は飼育量が非常に少なかった
You can tell it started almost 20 years ago
調べてみると約20年前に始まったそうです
This growth rate is rapidly increasing
この成長率は急速に高まっています
Can you see this number?
この数字が見えますか？
8% annual growth rate
年間成長率 8%
2012 is last year
2012年は去年です
Farmed production is 66 million metric tons
養殖生産量は6,600万トン
70,000 metric tons this year
今年は7万トン
So by 20 years maybe 20 years
だから20年までには20年くらいかな
The yield of farming will be higher than that of old fish
養殖の収量は古い魚よりも高くなります
So this industry is developing
だからこの業界は発展してるんだよ
demand is rapidly increasing
需要が急速に増加している
so it's a trend
だからそれがトレンドなんだよ
Just mentioned it is until 2018
先ほども言いましたが、2018年までです
Then farming will exceed the amount of catch
そうすれば養殖は漁獲量を超えるだろう
Well so these only depend on so although farming to provide
まあ、これらは農業が提供するものにのみ依存しますが、
Then let's see where Taiwan ranks
それでは台湾が何位なのか見てみましょう
Taiwan although we have a large fleet catching fish
台湾には大規模な船団が魚を捕獲していますが、
still catch this squid
このイカを捕まえる
But we have limited fish species to catch
でも釣れる魚種は限られている
So even though we are like this
だから、こんな私たちだけど
Taiwan catches fish all over the world
台湾は世界中の魚を捕獲します
Up to 15 million tons in China
中国では最大1,500万トン
Taiwan is 850,000 metric tons
台湾は85万トン
That fights against the one percent of the world
それは世界の1パーセントと戦う
In fact, we don't catch much
実はあまり釣れないんです
But what we catch is more expensive fish
でも私たちが獲るのはもっと高価な魚だ
This is how much we make up
これが私たちが補う金額です
What about breeding?
繁殖についてはどうですか？
What about us in Taiwan?
台湾ではどうですか？
Because we are limited to our area
地域限定なので
but what about our output
しかし、私たちの出力はどうでしょうか
About 310,000 metric tons
約31万トン
Then China is more than 47 million metric tons
すると中国は4,700万トン以上
So this amount is very large
なのでこの金額はかなり大きいです
Then Taiwan and world production is 0.10%
すると台湾と世界の生産量は0.10%
So but we use small things to make big things
しかし、私たちは小さなことを使って大きなことを成し遂げます
We have good industrial technology
私たちは優れた産業技術を持っています
Then let's replace our yield
それでは、収量を置き換えてみましょう
So our quantity is definitely small
ですので、量は間違いなく少ないです
But the level of technology we have to present
しかし、私たちが提示しなければならない技術のレベルは、
So
それで
So look at the world
だから世界を見てみろよ
Not only Taiwan
台湾だけじゃないよ
From the perspective of the world
世界から見ると
This is the maximum yield
これが最大収量です
because oysters
牡蠣だから
It is only 12 million tons
たったの1200万トンです
but in terms of fish
でも魚に関しては
The first one is mostly because of China
一つ目は主に中国のせい
keep a lot of carp
鯉をたくさん飼う
3.5 million tons a year
年間350万トン
The second most is this shrimp
2番目に多いのがこのエビです
3.8 million tons
380万トン
The third is no abalone
3つ目はアワビではありません
is 2.85 million tons
285万トンです
Salmon is 1.7 million tons
サーモンは170万トン
probably can see
おそらく見える
When your fish species are all million tons
あなたの魚種がすべて100万トンの場合
output to develop
開発するためのアウトプット
so so we this
それで、それで私たちはこれ
exist
存在
In terms of the world or Taiwan
世界というか台湾という観点から見ると
Then it can be seen from the above analysis that
次に、上記の分析から次のことがわかります。
The importance of nutrients
鮮養質重要性
so
それで
this
これ
Because fresh nutrients
新鮮な栄養素なので、
output can
出力できる
with your amount
あなたの金額で
So
それで
More importantly, in animal feed
さらに重要なのは、動物の飼料において
We often say that cost is feed conversion power
コストはフィード変換電力であるとよく言います。
It is Fit Conversion Ration, FCR
フィット換算比、FCRです
As for fish farming, the feed is very good now
魚の養殖に関しては、今は飼料が非常に良いです
Some 1.2 to 1.5 kg of feed
飼料約1.2～1.5kg
1 kg of fish will grow out
1kgの魚が成長します
But what about the kilogram statistics
しかし、キログラム統計はどうでしょうか
this, this
これこれ
What about this, this grass-rock sports animal?
この草岩の動物はどうでしょうか？
About 8 kg of feed
餌約8kg
Is it better to add 7, it is 2
7を足したほうがいいですか、2です
But the conversion efficiency of fish is more
しかし、魚の変換効率はもっと高いです
Then, more importantly
それから、もっと重要なことは、
For the identification of farmed diseases
農場で発生した病気の特定のために
Disease detection, what about medical technology?
病気の検出、医療技術についてはどうですか?
It's quite mature now
もうかなり成熟してきましたね
What about research in this area in Taiwan?
台湾におけるこの分野の研究はどうなっているのでしょうか？
A considerable amount of research has also been invested in
かなりの量の研究も投資されています
Well, for the health mentioned just now
さて、先ほどの健康についてですが、
and food safety
そして食品の安全性
That aquatic product is very important
その水産物はとても重要です
In particular, we mentioned that apart from talking about high-quality protein
特に、高品質のタンパク質についての話とは別に、
This, this fish meat still has very elegant
これ、この魚肉はまだ非常にエレガントです
collection
コレクション
then this is
それならこれは
There is no way to provide the meat we are talking about
私たちが話している肉を提供する方法はありません
So in terms of health needs
健康上のニーズという点では
it is very important
それは非常に重要です
so i mention one more number
それで、もう一つ数字を言います
just mentioned numbers
先ほど数字を挙げました
is our seed balance
私たちのシードバランスは
then 1.2 million metric tons
その後120万トン
Then there are about 300,000 to 450,000 metric tons in breeding
その後、約 300,000 ～ 450,000 トンが繁殖に使用されます。
About 28%
約28%
What about the output value?
出力値はどうなるのでしょうか？
Taiwan's remaining output value is about 100 billion
台湾の残りの生産額は約1000億
Breeding about 38 billion
約380億匹が繁殖
That output value accounted for 35.7%
その生産額は35.7％を占めた
Indicates the value of the rest of the breeding
残りの繁殖の価値を示します
Slightly higher than Yu Lao's calm value
ユウラオの穏やかな値よりわずかに高い
We understand Taiwan's international
私たちは台湾の国際性を理解しています
We farm
私たちは農業をしています
some of our status
私たちのステータスの一部
After this pros and cons
この後のメリットとデメリット
Let's look at Taiwan in
台湾を見てみましょう
Sorry
ごめん
Strategies for development in this area of ​​marine biotechnology in Taiwan
台湾における海洋バイオテクノロジーのこの分野の発展戦略
Of course we usually talk about strategy
もちろん、私たちは戦略について話すことが多いです
usually do a
通常は
Analysis of some pros and cons
いくつかの長所と短所の分析
digital analysis
デジタル分析
Just now I mentioned that Taiwan has these characteristics
先ほど台湾にはこんな特徴があると言いました
We are often proud to say
私たちはよく誇りを持ってこう言います
Taiwan's farming technology
台湾の農業技術
and feed technology
と飼料技術
The technology of the viewing instrument is carefully selected
觀賞儀的技術都詳意選球
This is not a problem
これは問題ではありません
Second we have a lot of talent
第二に、私たちはたくさんの才能を持っています
The third one is that we have very close cooperation in industry, relations and academia
3つ目は、産業界、関係界、学術界で非常に緊密な協力関係にあることです。
our chance is
私たちのチャンスは
We are able to develop multifaceted outcomes
多面的な成果を生み出すことができます
including industrial applications
産業用途を含む
Applications in the medical industry
医療業界での応用
Ours is structured
私たちのものは構造化されています
Asia-Pacific's Aquatic Total Second Center for this condition
この症状に対するアジア太平洋地域の水生トータル第 2 センター
Because regardless of mainland China
なぜなら中国本土に関係なく
or Southeast Asian countries
または東南アジア諸国
They all went to Taiwan to ask for talent
彼らは才能を求めて台湾へ行きました
Need technology
技術が必要です
This is indeed where we are going to develop
ここがまさに私たちが開発するところです
But we also have some points
しかし、私たちにもいくつかのポイントがあります
for example
例えば
Industry relocation
産業移転
Technology integration is not good enough
テクノロジーの統合は十分ではない
insufficient funds
残高不足
Natural resources are scarce
天然資源は希少です
We've been trying to find ways to overcome him recently.
私たちは最近、彼を克服する方法を見つけようとしています。
The third is research strength
3つ目は研究力です
I want to report to you about my research strength
私の研究力について報告したいです
is our laboratory
私たちの研究室です
I went to such a long time for a study
とても長い間勉強に行ってきました
in manor circle
マナーサークルで
Because I just said as the Generalissimo
私は総司令官として言っただけだから
There is also some burden on aquatic technology
水産技術にもある程度の負担がある
We do part of the planning and promotion work
企画・プロモーション業務の一部を行っております
So our laboratory is of course still based on
したがって、私たちの研究室はもちろん今でも
molecular biology
分子生物学
economic research
経済調査
to study important aquatic farmed animals
重要な水生養殖動物を研究する
animal with pattern
模様のある動物
then research
それから研究する
Then we address important topics
次に、重要なトピックについて説明します
boneless fish
骨なしの魚
Grouper
ハタ
and zebrafish
そしてゼブラフィッシュ
ornamental fish etc.
観賞魚など
These are the objects of our research
これらは私たちの研究の対象です
Then the subject will grow against it
そうすれば主題はそれに対して成長するでしょう
Because of raising this animal
この動物を育てたせいで
growing
成長している
Speed ​​is an important source of determining its income
スピードは収入を決定する重要な要素です
You grow fast, it has a yield and payback will be quicker
成長が早く、収量があり、回収も早くなります
Second, as environmental changes and disease risks are reduced
第二に、環境の変化と病気のリスクが軽減されるため、
So growing is, usually breeding
つまり、成長することは通常、繁殖することです
No matter from breeding to feed flowering is the most important part
育種から開花ま​​でが最も重要な部分です
The second is disease monitoring and disease prevention
2 つ目は疾病のモニタリングと疾病の予防です。
Often breeding inside now the world statistics
現在世界の統計では国内で繁殖していることが多い
About 40% of losses due to disease deaths
損失の約40％は病気による死亡によるもの
So the disease can sometimes even reach 100%
そのため、病気の感染率が 100% に達することもあります。
Therefore, disease prevention is very important
したがって、病気の予防は非常に重要です
Ornamental instrument
装飾楽器
Taiwan is a viewing instrument and is currently on the top of the international
台湾は注目のツールであり、現在は国際世界のトップにあります。
still the most competitive country
依然として最も競争力のある国
Competing with us is mainly Singapore
私たちと競合するのは主にシンガポールです
Singapore used Southeast Asia for its Forte acquisition
シンガポールはフォルテ買収に東南アジアを利用した
it transfer center
それ転送センター
We in Taiwan really have four to five hundred kinds of ornamental instruments
台湾には実に400～500種類の装飾楽器がある
in Taiwan
台湾で
That is exported from Taiwan
台湾から輸出されているものです
So we are actually more advanced than Singapore and more advanced in the industry.
したがって、実際にはシンガポールよりも進んでおり、業界でも進んでいます。
Then we have our advantage
そうすれば我々には利点がある
Then the question of guilt
次に罪悪感の問題
Then I just mentioned that there are some unsuitable technologies to be imported
それから、輸入には不適当な技術があると先ほど申し上げました。
Then let this industry develop
それならこの業界を発展させましょう
The following are the topics
以下がトピックスです
let everyone know
みんなに知らせて
Therefore, our research topic will be selected from this excellent tracing
したがって、私たちの研究テーマは、この優れたトレースの中から選択されることになります。
Especially for those who have no national interest
特に国益を持たない人にとっては
The second one is that we build this technology of gene transfer
2つ目は、この遺伝子導入技術を構築することです。
Then the third is the growth path
3つ目は成長経路です
Low temperature resistance is also useful for industrial development
耐低温性は産業発展にも役立つ
Especially fluorescent viewing technology
特に蛍光観察技術
Our team does a pretty good job of working with the industry
私たちのチームは業界との協力において非常に良い仕事をしています
That's because it's a gene rotator
それは遺伝子ローテーターだからです
So we need a suitable platform to build
したがって、構築するには適切なプラットフォームが必要です
It is more important that we do a good job in technical research
技術研究をしっかり行うことがより重要です
So let's look at this excellent
それで、この素晴らしいものを見てみましょう
This is what everyone needs to know
これは誰もが知っておくべきことです
any of us
私たちの誰か
You need to produce economically for this animal and plant
この動植物を経済的に生産する必要があります
Then you have to go through preseeding
次に、事前シード処理を行う必要があります
What about pre-planting?
植え付け前はどうするの？
Then you have to inherit the genetic method
それなら遺伝的方法を継承しなければなりません
that is, selected
つまり選択された
genetic traits
遺伝的特徴
Then your characteristic, for example, is to grow.
そうすると、例えばあなたの特性は成長することです。
Wait, what about the different features you want to choose?
ちょっと待って、選択したいさまざまな機能についてはどうですか?
Then you have to go through its quantification
次に、その定量化を行う必要があります
Then look at its gene, this
それからその遺伝子を見てください、これは
its this trade
それはこの取引です
What about the mark of this gene?
この遺伝子のマークはどうなるのでしょうか？
can identify it
それを特定できる
as pre-seed
プレシードとして
For example, if you grow up, you want to
たとえば、大人になったらこうなりたい
fast growing
急成長
large fish
大きな魚
the fish
的魚
no fish
無過魚
Then you pick the front end
次に、フロントエンドを選択します
That can grow up to 800g fish
最大800gの魚まで成長可能
streaming fish
流れる魚
then continue breeding
その後は繁殖を続ける
so you can
だからあなたはできる
You can pre-seed
事前にシードすることができます
grow fast
早く成長する
big fish
大きな魚
Then you can produce it
それなら生産できるよ
What about the other inherited traits?
他の遺伝的特性についてはどうですか？
We can also pass this
これも渡すことができます
this this this genetic this
これこれこれ遺伝子これ
mark to filter
フィルターにマークを付ける
that due to the development of molecular biology
それは分子生物学の発展によるものです
This property of genes can be established
遺伝子のこの性質は確立できる
So now combine
それで今結合します
molecular genetic marker of DNA
DNAの分子遺伝マーカー
Generations of genetic variants can be shortened
遺伝的変異の世代を短縮できる
That is, the time can be reduced
つまり時間も短縮できる
So in the past, for example
そこで過去には、例えば
It takes 8 years for you to inherit the inheritance
遺産相続まで8年かかる
Inherited markers combined with DNA
DNAと結合した遺伝マーカー
Can shorten the time by about half
時間を約半分に短縮できる
So accelerated genetics
遺伝学が加速した
Allows the industry to develop
業界の発展を可能にする
So it is the auxiliary relic that becomes the mark
補助遺物が目印となるわけですね
there is a marker
マーカーがあります
In the past there was no marker
昔は標識なんてなかったのに
then inside
それから中に
The old man who defends me is advanced enough
私を守ってくれる老人は十分に進歩している
That's before you grow up
それは大人になる前のこと
I have a marker that says
というマーカーがあります
With this marker, it will grow bigger
このマーカーを付けると大きくなります
So for this marker, you first use the firmness of DNA
このマーカーでは、まず DNA の硬さを利用します。
Then you can leave this
じゃあ、これは放っておいてもいいよ
Huanli Next Generation
環利次世代
So by doing this you can also reduce
こうすることで削減することもできます
This total time
この合計時間
so we
だから私たちは
We cooperate with aquatic leads
私たちは水生リードと協力しています
it has the same time
それは同じ時間です
These two body types can be different
これら 2 つの体型は異なる場合があります
nearly 50%
ほぼ50%
So we use
そこで私たちは使用します
For example, using traditional DNA
たとえば、伝統的な DNA を使用する
This marking of the RF LOP
RF LOPのこのマーキング
it can be seen
それは見ることができます
this grows fast
これは成長が早い
use this two different
この 2 つの異なるものを使用します
Limiting beauty of DNA to cut
DNAの美しさを切断に限定する
The pattern that these two become
この二人がなるパターン
Same as this original
このオリジナルと同じ
it's different from total
合計とは違います
So we went after these two
それで私たちはこの二人を追いかけました
This cut of HINF 1 and RASA 1
HINF 1 と RASA 1 のこのカット
fragments of DNA
DNAの断片
Then you can have a marker
それからマーカーを付けることができます
This is already considered traditional
これはすでに伝統的なものと考えられています
There is a way
やり方がある
Then use a markup like this
次に、次のようなマークアップを使用します
then you can also choose to say
次に、次のように言うこともできます
Why choose no national language
なぜ国語を選ばないのか
All-male stateless
男性のみが無国籍
Because there is no national language
国語がないから
Everyone says it's good
みんな良いって言うよ
wonderful period more exciting
素晴らしい時期がさらに刺激的になります
but there is
しかし〜がある
XY's
XYさん
male
男
words with XX
XXがついた言葉
What about when only sexual fish are together?
性的な魚だけが一緒にいる場合はどうなるでしょうか？
Wu Guoyu is almost four months old
ウー・グオユウ君はもうすぐ生後4か月になります
He copulates as soon as he is sexually mature
性的に成熟するとすぐに交尾する
So if the fish is not big, he will only be the next generation
つまり、魚が大きくなければ、彼は次世代だけになります
That's a big one
それは大きなことだ
need to provide all
すべてを提供する必要がある
All the energy provided by him is
彼が提供するすべてのエネルギーは
Won't you go after your girlfriend?
あなたのガールフレンドを追いかけませんか？
so he grows big
だから彼は大きくなる
so so say look at us
だからそう言って、私たちを見てください
the quarter before the event
イベントの前四半期
There are so many Wu Guoyu
呉国宇はたくさんいる
Then they will all come after girlfriends
そうすれば彼らは皆ガールフレンドを追いかけるでしょう
live with him
彼と一緒に住む
In this round tide
この丸い潮流の中で
you have a chance to see
あなたには見るチャンスがあります
Extremely fun
とても楽しい
that now means
それは今意味します
How big does Wu Guoyu have to be?
呉国宇はどのくらいの大きさですか?
Wu Guoyu can be raised to more than three kilograms
呉国宇は3キロ以上まで育てることができる
Three kilograms
3キログラム
So I'm going to Jiaoxi this weekend
ということで今週末は礁渓へ行きます
there is a restaurant
レストランがあります
because tv said
テレビが言ってたから
Wu Guoyu can become a restaurant's family
呉国宇はレストランの家族になれる
and very expensive
そして非常に高価な
One customer needs to go alone
お客さん一人で行く必要がある
Of course not eating Wu Guoyu directly
もちろん呉国宇を直接食べるわけではありません
He still eats class ten
彼はまだクラス10を食べています
Nine holes and so on
ナインホールなど
But Wu Guoyu is playing the main role
でも呉国宇が主役だよ
he just wants
彼はただ欲しいだけです
Fish over 2.5kg
2.5kg以上の魚
He said that such a big fish is good
こんな大きな魚がいいよと彼は言った
will be strong and delicious
強くて美味しいでしょう
really good
とてもいいです
too small fish
小さすぎる魚
Turtle meat is soft
亀の肉は柔らかいです
After arriving there, it will be full of this angular diameter
そこに到着すると、この角直径でいっぱいになります
And the fish is quite sweet
そして魚はとても甘いです
i mean
つまり
super male turtle fish
スーパー雄カメフィッシュ
That's also sifting with potato marcos
それもポテトマルコスと一緒にふるいにかけます
So of course we've also been using the new Marco lately
もちろん最近は新しいマルコも使っています
is called microRNA
マイクロRNAと呼ばれます
fragments of microRNA
マイクロRNAの断片
as a new marker for growth
成長の新たな指標として
So we analyze
そこで分析します
also get the new tag
新しいタグも取得します
can be used as molecular marker screening
分子マーカーのスクリーニングとして使用可能
related to growth
成長に関わる
the second one
2番目のもの
Because of the first rotor technique
初のローターテクニックにより
like everyone said a lot
みんながよく言ったように
How to use it in fish
魚での使い方
Let us introduce to you
ご紹介しましょう
this is very beautiful
これはとても美しいです
Because Taiwan can be said to be the only one in the world
台湾は世界で唯一とも言えるので
the fastest
最速
It is through the precise technology of fish
それは魚の精密な技術によるものです
Trained from small chairs to medium chairs
小型の椅子から中型の椅子までトレーニング
even to large chairs
大きな椅子にも
in various colors
さまざまな色で
green, red, yellow
緑、赤、黄
we can become a beautiful
私たちは美しくなれる
And very vivid new colorful world of fish
そしてとても鮮やかな新しいカラフルな魚の世界
So goldfish eggs are not just for ornamental fish
金魚の卵は観賞魚だけではありません
We can also use it
私たちも使えますよ
If you grow faster
もっと早く成長すれば
disease resistance, resistance
耐病性、抵抗力
Increase feed conversion
フィードコンバージョンの増加
basic research
基礎研究
can also be promoted
昇進することもできる
Increase nutritional value
栄養価を高める
genome research, etc.
ゲノム研究など。
All kinds of fish can play different roles
あらゆる種類の魚が異なる役割を果たします
role of research purpose
研究目的の役割
Understand the technology of the new transfer
新しいトランスファーのテクノロジーを理解する
we know in simple terms
私たちは簡単な言葉で知っています
It is the color body of our plastid
それは私たちの色素体のカラーボディです
you cut through the first known
あなたは最初に知られたものを切り開いた
you can put the gene you want
欲しい遺伝子を入れることができる
Put it in this plastid
この色素体に入れてください
into this plastid of such a recombinant BNA
このような組換えBNAの色素体に
So, for example, we put in the genes of foreign aid
たとえば、外国援助の遺伝子を組み込んだのです
For example, the production base will grow fast
例えば、生産拠点が急速に成長する
Or this epitope that we put in Star Qiannian
あるいは、Star Qiannian に置いたこのエピトープ
Then there will be vaccines and so on in the future.
それから将来的にはワクチンなども出てくるでしょう。
Make medical protein
医療用プロテインを作る
What about after putting it in?
入れた後はどうでしょうか？
What about this plastid?
この色素体はどうでしょうか？
Beat into the egg box of the fish's fertilized eggs
魚の有精卵を卵箱に叩き込む
So what happens after the gene for foreign aid enters?
では、外国援助の遺伝子が入った後はどうなるでしょうか？
The gene of this foreign aid
この外国援助の遺伝子
For example production base then it will cut into this fish
例えば生産拠点ならこの魚に切り込みます
For example, this case is salmon
たとえば、このケースはサーモンです
Then it goes inside this dyed bottom
それからこの染まった底の中に入ります
So because of the production base
生産拠点のせいで
Imported this salmon, it grows faster
このサーモンは輸入されており、成長が早いです
In fact it's already licensed to do this in the U.S.
実際、米国ではすでにこれを行うことが許可されています。
This genetically modified fish should be transferred commercially
この遺伝子組み換え魚は商業的に譲渡されるべきである
What about the conversion technology?
変換技術についてはどうですか？
I'm just going to talk to you guys very quickly.
早速皆さんにお話したいと思います。
earliest start
最最最早開始
Started with this microinjection method
このマイクロインジェクション法から始まりました
The straight DNA just mentioned
先ほど述べたストレートDNA
you load in very thin capillaries
非常に細い毛細管にロードします
Then its capillary is very stretched 0.1-0.5
その後、その毛細管は0.1〜0.5に非常に引き伸ばされます。
microscopic glass needle for microphone
マイク用の極小ガラス針
that's under the microscope
それは顕微鏡の下です
The DNA you hooked this pin
このピンを引っ掛けた DNA
Plastic eggs beaten to one cell stage
プラスチックの卵を 1 細胞段階まで叩く
Then you don't care about it after typing in
そうすれば、入力した後は気にしなくなります
let it float
浮かせてみましょう
Next, the identification of DNA and the screening of its appearance
次に、DNAの同定とその外観のスクリーニング
Can it grow faster
もっと早く成長できるでしょうか
Or are they more resistant to disease?
それとも病気に対する抵抗力が強いのでしょうか？
This micro-injection is not the most technical
このマイクロインジェクションは最も技術的なものではありません
So besides this technology
したがって、このテクノロジー以外にも
What about the second technique?
2番目のテクニックはどうでしょうか？
because we know the egg
私たちは卵を知っているので
It's an egg membrane and a cell membrane
卵膜と細胞膜です
So use the film to create space
フィルムを使って空間を作る
Just use Electoral Polition
選挙政治を使用するだけです
is to use instantaneous high voltage
瞬間的な高電圧を使用することです
For example, 2000V, 3000V
例：2000V、3000V
Use the non-second method
2 番目以外の方法を使用する
electrical stimulation
電気刺激
you put the indented egg
あなたは凹んだ卵を置きます
Soak in the hands of straight DNA
ストレートDNAの手に浸る
easy inside
簡単な内部
After electrical stimulation
電刺激以後
The cell membrane will fluctuate momentarily
細胞膜が瞬間的に変動する
DNA goes into the egg
DNAは卵の中に入る
So this can also achieve fast DNA transfer
したがって、これにより高速な DNA 転送も実現できます。
soak in the egg
卵に浸す
The third method is to compare artificial cell membranes
3つ目は人工細胞膜を比較する方法です。
That is to say
つまり
We know that the structure of the cell membrane is a
細胞膜の構造は次のとおりであることがわかっています。
gelatin membrane
ゼラチン膜
The gelatinous film can be artificially made into a
ゼラチン状の膜を人工的に作ることができます。
Pointing style is Legislative Shuang
指差しスタイルは立法双です
So this Lipson, we'll take the DNA,
それでこのリプソン、DNAを採取します
Plastid DNA is packed inside this Lipson
このリプソンの中に色素体DNAが詰め込まれている
So its structural properties are similar to cell membranes
そのため、その構造特性は細胞膜に似ています
then our cells
それから私たちの細胞
then when this, this, this
それから、これ、これ、これ
What about this plastid?
この色素体はどうでしょうか？
Then put it in this, this, this
それから、これ、これ、これに入れてください
What's inside this substance?
この物質の中には何が入っているのでしょうか？
What about when it hits the cell membrane?
それが細胞膜に到達するとどうなるでしょうか？
We undergo either electrical stimulation
どちらかの電気刺激を受ける
Either or use, use this
どちらかを使用するか、これを使用してください
This PEG is
このPEGは
The diameter of Polyacin glycol
ポリアシングリコールの直径
it fuses, the cell membrane fuses
融合する、細胞膜が融合する
Then the DNA is sent into the cell
その後、DNAが細胞内に送られます
this is, this
これはこれです
It can be achieved by the method of cell membrane fusion
細胞膜融合という方法で実現できます
What about this commonly used one?
よく使われるこのものはどうでしょうか？
It is the method of using, using viruses, vectors
ウイルス、ベクターを利用する、利用する方法です。
there are some viruses
いくつかのウイルスがあります
it can
できる
Infection, what about the genes of foreign aid?
感染症、外国援助の遺伝子はどうなるのでしょうか？
Through the infection process?
感染プロセスを通じて？
Then it goes into the cell
それから細胞に入ります
For example, like viruses, Novirus
たとえば、ウイルスのように、ノウイルス
Then it can be loaded with the genes of foreign aid
そうすれば外国援助の遺伝子を組み込むことができる
So we can put the gene of our foreign aid
それで私たちは対外援助の遺伝子を組み込むことができます
loaded in this viral vector
このウイルスベクターに組み込まれている
Let it infect this sperm or egg
この精子または卵子に感染させてください
Then the gene can be transmitted in
そうすれば、遺伝子は次のように伝達されます。
so there are various ways
だからいろいろな方法があります
Because the development of scientific research can be re-applied
科学研究の発展は再応用できるから
But basically everyone is still the most commonly used
しかし、基本的には誰もが依然として最も一般的に使用されています
with this microcolumn method
このマイクロカラム法では
Or this radio wave method to do gene transfer
あるいはこの電波法で遺伝子導入を行う
then in the research
それから研究で
Because of Yilie's research
イリーの研究のせいで
Everyone is trying their best to explore the function of genes
遺伝子の働きをみんなで探ろうと頑張っています
technology that can be combined with genetic modification
遺伝子組み換えと組み合わせることができる技術
to study the function of genes
遺伝子の機能を研究する
That was developed first in Iliad
それはイリアスで最初に開発されました
Then Gene proposes several methods
そこでジーンはいくつかの方法を提案する
Then they are very useful in research
そうすれば研究にとても役立ちます
Well, of course I won't go into details on this side.
まあ、もちろん、この面については詳しくは説明しません。
Nucleus method with Zinc Finger
ジンクフィンガーによる核法
Or Titan's method or Christophe Cass
タイタンのメソッドとかクリストフ・カスとか
These methods can all cause specific genes
これらの方法はすべて特定の遺伝子を引き起こす可能性があります
for example
例えば
So which gene of your fish destroys it
では、あなたの魚のどの遺伝子がそれを破壊するのか
What impact would it have to demonstrate the function of these genes
これらの遺伝子の機能を実証することはどのような影響を与えるでしょうか
We use this technology
私たちはこの技術を使用しています
Let's look at the research on growth promotion
成長促進に関する研究を見てみましょう
what we know best is
私たちが一番よく知っているのは
Growth of our vertebrates
私たちの脊椎動物の成長
It's the regulator that makes the lice nectar
シラミの蜜を作るのは調節装置です
the regulation of the endometrium basically it has an axis
子宮内膜の調節には基本的に軸があります
It is the square base of growth hormone is GHRH
成長ホルモンの四角い基礎となるのがGHRHです
It is secreted by Xia's ball in the brain
脳内の夏玉から分泌される
Xia's ball releases these religion hormones
Xia のボールはこれらの宗教ホルモンを放出します
It is to release the base to the pituitary gland
下垂体に基部を放出することです
The pituitary gland talks about this GHRG4G
下垂体はこの GHRG4G について話します
It starts to produce growth base is GH
成長基盤を生み出し始めるのがGH
After the growth base is released, it will be sent to the whole body
成長基盤がリリースされた後、全身に届けられます。
especially sent to the liver
特に肝臓に
What about the liver?
肝臓はどうですか？
It attacks this transgenic growth factor in the liver
肝臓にあるこのトランスジェニック成長因子を攻撃します
it also secretes
それも分泌する
that send to the muscles, bones, organs of the whole body
全身の筋肉、骨、臓器に送られる
So what about this IGF?
では、このIGFはどうでしょうか？
It's been half a year
半年が経ちました
A very important function of promoting cell proliferation
細胞増殖を促進する非常に重要な機能
So this becomes an axis for the growth of an inner honeyhog
これが内なるハニーホッグの成長の軸となるのですね
So what do we do based on this axis
では、この軸に基づいて何をするか
let's discuss
話し合いましょう
So what the hell is Gross Hormone in the fish?
では、魚の総ホルモンとは一体何なのでしょうか？
to promote growth?
成長を促進するには？
How to apply its physiological mechanism to do research
その生理学的メカニズムを研究に応用する方法
That's what I mentioned just now
それが私が今言ったことです
through
終えた
The earliest of this growth base
この成長基盤の最初期
What about job transfer?
転勤についてはどうですか？
into the mouse
マウスの中へ
By 1980
1980年までに
then it can make the mouse
それからマウスを作ることができます
This Gross Hormone that accepted the outer circularity
外周性を受け入れたこのグロスホルモン
It's long
それは長い
It's this original this this this this this mouse
これがオリジナルです、これ、これ、このマウスです。
two to three times as large
2～3倍の大きさ
Proof that genetic modification
遺伝子組み換えの証拠
The growth technique through gene expression
遺伝子発現による増殖技術
It can grow individually
個別に成長できる
So this technology is a dream for everyone
つまり、このテクノロジーは誰にとっても夢なのです
Then we can wave to other animals
そうすれば他の動物たちに手を振ることができます
A similar technique can be used
同様のテクニックを使用できます
so this is
それでこれは
the first to meet
最初に会う人
The growth of idioms
イディオムの成長
So they put the growth technology
そこで彼らは成長テクノロジーを導入しました
get the rules
ルールを理解する
so at the same time
それで同時に
It has the greatest difference
一番大きな違いがあるのは
so big
とても大きく
So of course this should
もちろんこれはそうすべきです
Compliance with biosafety assessment
バイオセーフティ評価への準拠
their individual stocks are fixed
彼らの個別株は固定されている
Hingel standard
Hingel標準
That technique has been used
そのテクニックが使われている
the carp
鯉
this big
この大きな
this is the original
これがオリジナルです
Or Channel Catfish
またはチャネルナマズ
It's an anchovies
アンチョビです
or turtle fish etc.
または亀の魚など。
So to prove a theory like this
したがって、このような理論を証明するには
with technology it is feasible
テクノロジーがあれば実現可能だ
So
それで
So we first
だから私たちはまず最初に
also come
も来てください
Look at this just-like guideline growth factor
見てください、このガイドラインそっくりの成長因子
IGF
IGF
unbroken growth
途切れることのない成長
Then we use this injection or oral method
次に、この注射または経口方法を使用します
also prove these
これらも証明してください
it uses it to compare growth factors
成長因子を比較するために使用します
It promotes growth without heal
治癒せずに成長を促進します
In terms of weight and length
重さと長さの点で
Probably more than 20%
おそらく20％以上
Growth and weight gain in ten weeks
10週間の成長と体重増加
means that we regulate growth
つまり成長を調節するということです
Nemi's system
ネミのシステム
Can achieve the effect of promoting growth
成長促進効果が得られる
Then, due to the development of the genome research
その後、ゲノム研究の発展により、
we feel like saying
私たちは言いたい気分です
Except IGF
IGFを除く
Get stimulated by Brosch Hormone
ブロッシュホルモンで刺激を受ける
to promote growth
成長を促進するために
Are there any other factors
他の要因はありますか
So what we express through our genes
では、私たちが遺伝子を通じて表現しているものは、
screening of the system
システムのスクリーニング
Then we found a new growth factor
そして新たな成長因子を発見
is it coley
コーリーですか？
Protein premise, the name is a bit longer
プロテイン前提、名前は少し長いです
We call it Provenaning
私たちはそれを証明と呼んでいます
Then this is considered Chinese after typing
入力後、これは中国語とみなされます
This granule protein will be expressed if it is
この顆粒タンパク質は、
that expresses what we think it has to do with growth
それは成長と関係があると私たちが考えていることを表しています
So we're going to prove it's functional
それで、それが機能することを証明するつもりです
We transfer to this zebrafish through the elite
私たちはエリートを通じてこのゼブラフィッシュに移植します
so so live a carrier
それで、キャリアとして生きています
Then after elite transfer
その後エリート移籍後
It is also found that whether public
公開されているかどうかもわかります。
or female zebrafish
またはメスのゼブラフィッシュ
If elites who exhibit this granulin premise
この粒状の前提を示すエリートであれば、
words that can show
見せられる言葉
It can gain up to 48% of its body weight
体重の最大48%まで増加する可能性があります
Weight can be increased by 18.6% or 13.6%
重量は18.6%または13.6%増加可能
So there is a function like this
そこでこのような関数があります
So of course we're going to talk about it
もちろんそれについて話します
Mechanisms through which cellular transmission
細胞感染のメカニズム
to allow muscles to accelerate growth
筋肉の成長を促進するために
So we also identify it after MET
したがって、MET の後にもそれを識別します
The growth of COVID-19 outbound
新型コロナウイルス感染症のアウトバウンドの増加
The second is disease
2つ目は病気です
We know that Taiwan raises dead panfish
台湾が死んだパンフィッシュを飼育していることはわかっています
is the most famous internationally
国際的に最も有名です
Vaccines for Dead Squid
死んだイカのワクチン
often die from viral infection
ウイルス感染で死ぬことも多い
in the vaccine phase
ワクチン段階では
It is the stage of corruption
腐敗の段階です
Most important viral infection of the nerve necrosis virus
神経壊死ウイルスの最も重要なウイルス感染症
So we check for it
それで、それをテストしてみます
Research on vaccines related to novel RNA
新規RNAに関するワクチンの研究
We did some new research
私たちはいくつかの新しい研究を行いました
neuronecrosis virus
神経壊死ウイルス
Almost a vaccine against dead panfish
死んだパンフィッシュに対するほぼワクチン
in the fisherman's stage
漁師のステージで
90% or even 90% will die
90％、あるいは90％が死亡する
So immigration has always existed
つまり移民は常に存在していた
So how can we develop healthy vaccines
では、どうすれば健康的なワクチンを開発できるのでしょうか
is an important subject
重要な主題です
So for vaccine development
そこでワクチン開発については、
becomes a
になる
Vaccination is an important issue for viral infection
ウイルス感染症にはワクチン接種が重要
So this becomes an industry
それでこれが産業になる
but you have to avoid some research
ただし、いくつかの調査は避けなければなりません
fish immune system
魚の免疫システム
to be able to understand
理解できるようになる
So I won't go into details
したがって、これらについては詳しく説明しません
It really can become an industry
本当に産業化できる
then another
それからもう一つ
People or pigs or chickens
人とか豚とか鶏とか
You can keep playing for a second
1秒間プレイし続けることができます
It is very troublesome to keep fighting fish
常に魚と格闘するのは非常に面倒です
If you grab it, it won't collapse
掴めば崩れない
maybe it's possible
たぶんそれは可能です
under too much pressure
過度のプレッシャーの下で
so go to the body
それで体に行きます
it cannot adapt to life and death
生と死に適応できない
So I must develop
だから私は開発しなければならない
no injection
注射なし
is it possible to use this
これを使用することは可能ですか
deduction method
控除方法
So we have something like this
このようなものがあります
so we put
だから私たちは置きます
The vaccine is loaded in the
ワクチンが仕込まれている
This nanoscale
このナノスケールは
This Lipso
このリプソ
Feed this zebrafish inside
このゼブラフィッシュに餌をあげてください
then we have this one time
それから、これは一度だけです
Then I saw this red and silver light, which means it has eaten it.
すると、赤と銀の光が見えました。これは、それが食べられたことを意味します。
Then after 20 hours still
それから20時間経ってもまだ
In those 28 hours, it will slowly go to other parts of the body
28時間以内に、ゆっくりと体の他の部分に行きます。
place to go
行く場所
means that we use nanoscale
ナノスケールを使用することを意味します
this this topic
この話題
then you can put
それから置くことができます
through
透過
The absorption of Tibetan coins can enter
チベットコインの吸収が入る可能性があります
inside the body for teleportation
テレポーテーションのために体内に
So we put this virus
それで私たちはこのウイルスを入れました
fragment of this RNA
このRNAの断片
Then as the development of vaccines
それからワクチンの開発として
So
それで
selected a different segment
別のセグメントを選択しました
Then look at its ability to resist disease
次に、病気に抵抗する能力を見てみましょう
So we use this intrusive
したがって、この侵入的なものを使用します
the nucleic acid
核酸
What about RNA vaccines?
RNAワクチンについてはどうですか？
So
それで
if this virus
もしこのウイルスが
to infect
感染する
Shiban can do this too
シバンもこれできるよ
Its survival rate is 39%
その生存率は39％です
What about the treatment of the RNA of the Kouwu vaccine?
Kouwu ワクチンの RNA の処理についてはどうですか?
survival rate
生存率
can be increased to 67%
67%まで増加可能
This is what we are declaring
これが私たちが宣言していることです
can be seen
見られます
new like this
このような新しい
Development of Vaccine and Delivery Technology
ワクチンと送達技術の開発
can come come come
来てもいいよ来てもいいよ
But how much virus
しかし、ウイルスの量はどれくらい
With a company that has this reduction technology
この削減技術を持つ会社と
comparative physical techniques
比較身体技術
Simply put, it uses iron oxide
簡単に言うと酸化鉄を使っているのですが、
Becoming a Nanoscale Chef
ナノスケールシェフになる
The chef can pick up the antibody of the virus
シェフはウイルスの抗体を検出できる
Antibodies will catch the virus
抗体がウイルスを捕まえる
So catch more viruses
したがって、より多くのウイルスを捕まえます
This magnet is iron oxide
この磁石は酸化鉄です
When starting in the magnetic field
磁界中で始動する場合
turning fast
速く回る
It is of course combined with the virus later
もちろん後からウイルスと結合します
it turns slower
回転が遅くなります
So we can use this technique to quantify
したがって、この手法を使用して定量化できます。
This technology must be used now
この技術は今すぐにでも使わなければなりません
The thorough network method of immune nucleic acid is different
免疫核酸の徹底したネットワーク方式は違います
and faster
そしてより速く
So this company it has
それでこの会社が持っているのは
Or foreign virus testing
外国のウイルス検査とか
The platform of instruments and services
機器とサービスのプラットフォーム
The third thing to talk about is
3番目に話すことは、
like winter
冬のように
Taiwan is often
台湾はよくある
No milkfish, no abalone
サバヒーもアワビもいない
This grouper is dying in large numbers
このハタが大量に死んでいる
sea ​​scales and so on
海の鱗など
what about this situation
この状況はどうですか
just because of the low temperature
ただ気温が低いせいで
if continued
続ければ
heaven smokes above
天国は上で煙を吸う
our farm animals
私たちの農場の動物たち
Responsible for great loss
多大な損失の責任を負う
this mass death
この大量死
So let's think about it
それでは、考えてみましょう
some fish are ugly
醜い魚もいる
Let's say we know
私たちは知っているとしましょう
like a carp it is just very ugly
鯉のように、それはただ非常に醜いです
you are still in winter
あなたはまだ冬にいます
So this one in the fish tooth is living happily
それで、この魚の歯の子は幸せに暮らしています
so we think
それで私たちは考えます
Like sea scales, without abalone, life is hard to see
海の鱗のように、アワビがなければ生命は見えにくい
because of its genetic
その遺伝のせいで
one
一個
So we try to say
そこで私たちはこう言おうとします
prove that
証明してください
which genes
どの遺伝子
genes associated with ugly
醜さに関係する遺伝子
fish
魚
Then we filter through the genes
次に遺伝子をフィルタリングします
transfer of genes
遺伝子の転移
and then prove that
そしてそれを証明してください
this
これ
which genes
どの遺伝子
It's related to the unsightly appearance of fish
それは魚の醜さに関係しています
Through this research we
この研究を通じて私たちは、
In fact, we can identify it
実際、私たちはそれを特定することができます
One base acid for muscle beauty
筋肉の美しさのための1つの塩基酸
special form
特別的form
Especially the form of M3
特にM3のフォルム
under low temperature
低温下で
it allows zebrafish
ゼブラフィッシュを許可します
improve its resistance
耐性を改善する
So we use a graph like this to say
したがって、次のようなグラフを使用して次のように言います。
zebrafish
ゼブラフィッシュ
Wild cooking and gene transfer cooking this base acid muscle beauty
野生の料理と遺伝子移入でこの塩基性の筋肉の美しさを調理
bring it down to 13 degrees C
13℃まで下げます
this boiled fish
この煮魚
it passes a minute
1分経ちます
look at its fish
その魚を見てください
It barely moves the pattern
模様はほとんど動かない
that is
あれは
Sure enough, there is no fixed file
案の定、固定ファイルはありません
But the genetically modified fish
しかし遺伝子組み換え魚は
This pattern keeps changing
このパターンは変わり続けます
It means that fish can adapt to this low temperature
魚はこの低温にも適応できるということです
So specific numbers
非常に具体的な数字
Wild fish at 13 degrees C it only
13℃の天然魚のみ
we measure
私たちは測定します
Its length is the perpetual motion of 20 centimeters
その長さは20センチメートルの永久運動です
But genetically modified it can move 190 centimeters forever
しかし遺伝子組み換えにより永遠に190センチメートルを移動できる
Indicates that it has acquired the ability to resist containing
封じ込めることに抵抗する能力を獲得していることを示します
because it provides enough energy
十分なエネルギーを供給してくれるので
make it this movement
この動きにしてください
As far as positive exercise can be maintained
積極的な運動を継続できる限り
Of course it starts from this energy
もちろんこのエネルギーから始まります
So we know that this fish
それで私たちはこの魚が
especially the sea fish
特に海の魚
What about ocean fish?
海の魚はどうでしょうか？
It's this OmegaSpray
それがこのオメガスプレーです
Very large
非常に大きい
That's like we know the turtle fish below
それは私たちが下のカメの魚を知っているようなものです
Other fish OmegaSpray
等魚類OmegaSpray
It is EPA DHA
EPA・DHAです
Most oils with DHA are especially rich
DHA最類的油脂特別多
So it has something to do with the anti-sea
つまり、それは対海と関係があります
At the same time it has the function of improving our human health
同時に人間の健康を改善する機能もあります
This effect has been very
この効果は非常に大きかったです
proved very clearly
非常に明確に証明されました
Sorry
ごめん
that we often say
私たちがよく言うこと
EPA it's twenty carbons
EPA それは炭素20です
There are five from this
この中から5つあります
left this
これを残しました
Kabocha Look like
卡博抄 Look like
Combination with five double swords
双剣5本との組み合わせ
This is the EPA
これはEPAです
to DHA is 22 carbons
DHAの炭素数は22です
It N3 has a combination of six double swords
N3は6本の双剣の組み合わせを持つ
So these two types of Omega3
この2種類のオメガ3は
proved
証明された
This is positive
これはポジティブです
For example, toddlers
たとえば、幼児
DHA is very important for brain development
DHAは脳の発達に非常に重要です
or health care for eyesight
または視力の健康管理
also very important
も非常に重要です
but for disease
しかし病気のため
prevent neovascular disease
血管新生疾患を予防する
Prevention of Excellence
優秀性の防止
prevent slow cancer
進行性のがんを予防する
or resistance garden
またはレジスタンスガーデン
or anti-brainization
または反脳化
Finally, there are specific numbers
最後に具体的な数字が出てきました
so the tv turns on
それでテレビがつきます
Both advertise EPA and DHA
どちらもEPAとDHAを宣伝しています
U2 turned out to be interesting
U2は面白いことがわかった
I don't talk about which one
どっちかについては話さない
what kind of sword
どのような剣ですか
Omega3 is about to advertise
Omega3 が宣伝しようとしています
They say in Taiwan
台湾ではこう言われます
sell fish oil in food
魚油を食品として販売する
Is it to be bought or written
買うものですか、それとも書くものですか
it is in taiwan
それは台湾にあります
The other party is selling the third
相手が3つ目を販売中
So there are many people who say they eat fish oil
だから魚油を食べているという人がたくさんいます
But if we start from this
しかし、ここから始めると
Get it from this food
この食べ物から摂取しましょう
is more important
の方が重要です
then let's discuss
それから話し合いましょう
Synthetic EPA and DHA
合成EPAとDHA
Where is the PASWARE it synthesized
合成したパスウェアはどこにありますか
then we're going to discuss
それから話し合いましょう
Well this is already proven
まぁこれはもう証明されてるけど
That is to say, in the liver
つまり肝臓では
to synthesize EPA and DHA
EPAとDHAを合成する
Then also through fat loss beauty
そして脂肪減少美容を通しても
or go fishy
あるいは胡散臭いことになる
Drive with this delicious food
美味しいものを食べながらドライブ
From this Sparktan
このスパークタンから
This Nino-Legacy
このニノレガシー
from vegetable oil
植物油から
EPA that can be turned into 20 carbons
炭素20個に変えられるEPA
With 22 carbon DHA
炭素数22のDHA入り
This N is Omega3
このNはオメガ3です
So so we use genetic modification
だから私たちは遺伝子組み換えを使うのです
Yanchangmei is combined with the still fund Meilai of different styles
ヤンチャンメイはさまざまなスタイルのスティルファンドメイライと組み合わされています
So we set up different gene transfer values
そこで、異なる遺伝子導入値を設定します。
Let it be able to express the Diata IV, Diata V, and Diata VI just mentioned, and still come in from the fund
先ほど述べた Diata IV、Diata V、Diata VI を表現できるようにし、なおかつファンドから入ってくるようにします。
We use molecular sound, electric current to prove its existence and gene expression
分子音や電流を使ってその存在や遺伝子発現を証明します
It's important that we measure the zebrafish we've transferred
移したゼブラフィッシュを測定することが重要です
EPA DHA, and its intermediate EPA
EPA DHAとその中間体EPA
This is WallTimes
こちらはウォールタイムズです
As a result, the amount of transfer value can be increased several times
その結果、譲渡額を数倍に増やすことが可能
It can be increased to 3 times to 5 times, which is probably the established number
3倍から5倍まで増やすことができますが、おそらくこれが確立された数字です
That's a published paper, and its performance is very low compared to ours
それは出版された論文であり、そのパフォーマンスは私たちの論文と比較して非常に低いです
So we can behave like this to fish like this
だから私たちはこのように行動して、このように釣りをすることができます
Gene expression we have unique place
遺伝子発現は私たちに特有の場所を持っています
Then through this performance
そして今回の公演を通して
Then let's see if this can increase
それでは、これが増えるかどうか見てみましょう
its disease resistance
その耐病性
Just now has the ability to improve anti-inflammation and anti-disease
ちょうど今、抗炎症と抗病気を改善する能力があります
So this graph tells us that
このグラフからわかることは、
Omega-3 job transfer language
オメガ 3 の転職言語
It is strong against trauma
トラウマに強い
is the viability of the VIP infection
VIP感染の生存可能性です
18% can be increased to 80%
18% を 80% まで増やすことができます
So disease resistance increases
それで耐病性が高まる
Resistance to staining at 12 degrees C
12℃での耐汚染性
It turns out that the death power is almost 100%
死亡力はほぼ100%であることが判明
Then it can be raised to a survivable temperature
その後、生存可能な温度まで上げることができます
So this indeed introduces the gene for Omega-3 synthesis
つまり、これは確かにオメガ3合成のための遺伝子を導入したことになる
Then it not only can increase the amount of EPA
そうすれば、EPAの量を増やすことができるだけでなく、
At the same time, it improves the disease resistance and infection resistance of the animal
同時に、動物の病気に対する抵抗力と感染に対する抵抗力を向上させます。
More importantly, our purpose is the future
さらに重要なのは、私たちの目的は未来です
These transfers look like a
これらの転送は次のようになります
Can we provide our
私たちのものを提供できますか？
EPA and DHA for good health
EPAとDHAで健康をサポート
So increasing the body would have no national benefit
したがって、増加することによる国民の利益はありません
is synthetic without EPA DHA
EPA DHAを含まない合成です
Will it be available in the future
将来的には利用可能になりますか
source of this
これの出典
Here's what we're going to do next
次に行うことは次のとおりです
The fifth item we are talking about now is the viewing instrument
私たちが今話している5番目のアイテムは、観察装置です。
The viewing instrument may be more pleasing to everyone.
視聴機器は誰にとってももっと喜ばれるかもしれません。
The industry of this ornamental instrument in Taiwan
台湾の装飾楽器産業
Then there are currently about four or five billion in output value.
それから現在生産額は約四十億、五十億ございます。
That's pretty impressive
それはかなり印象的です
then the industry
それから業界
The government especially in Pingtung's National Agricultural Biotechnology Park
政府、特に屏東の国立農業バイオテクノロジー園
It is the center of gravity of an ornamental instrument
装飾楽器の重心です
then raise it there
それからそこで上げます
Quarantine clearance over there
あそこの検疫クリアランス
Kaohsiung
高雄
Not by Kaohsiung Tiny Airport
高雄小空港ではありません
directly to countries around the world
世界中の国へ直接
I hope that Taiwan's technology for Impression is quite
台湾の印象技術はかなりのものだと思います
In this officialdom in Taiwan, there are people from all over the world
台湾のこの官庁には世界中から人々が集まっています
It must be in the hands of the electrician within 72 hours
72時間以内に電気技師の手に渡らなければなりません
So so, this one like this
それで、これはこんな感じ
This has production and sales in a park in a country
こちらは田舎の公園で製造・販売しております
it is a very important part
それはとても重要な部分です
So so such a technique
なるほど、そんなテクニックも
is genetically modified from Molecular Biology
分子生物学から遺伝子組み換えされたものです
It has been developing all the way
ずっと発展してきました
So about 10 years ago
それで10年くらい前に
this this this this
これこれこれこれ
As for the Taiwan and Hong Kong company, it took this silver
台湾と香港の会社はこの銀を取りました
As far as the green silver light, turn until the rice field chair
緑銀の光まで、田んぼの椅子まで回してください
So it led to this and this in Taiwan
台湾でのあれこれにつながった
The development of this industry of turning straight silver chairs
銀色の直椅子を回転させるこの産業の発展
So what about this command company in Pingtung?
では、屏東にあるこの指揮会社はどうでしょうか？
know that we have genetic modification and
私たちが遺伝子組み換えを行っていることを知り、
this gene this this this
この遺伝子これこれこれ
What about the silver gene?
シルバー遺伝子はどうなるのでしょうか？
Then transfer these genes to medium-sized
次に、これらの遺伝子を中型の細胞に移入します。
For example, Angelfish, Jiujianpolou
例: エンゼルフィッシュ、九剣宝楼
or
また
This is another fish
これは別の魚です
Such fish species are the most leading in the world
このような魚種は世界で最も有力です
And it has attracted the attention of the media of various countries
そして全国メディアの注目を集めた
just to report
報告するだけ
So
それで
Hey, it's so slow
やあ、とても遅いですね
that's pink
それはピンクです
genes from coral
サンゴ由来の遺伝子
go to angelfish
エンゼルフィッシュに行く
then changed the color of the fish
すると魚の色が変わりました
I'm not advertising for the company
私は会社の宣伝をしているわけではありません
I brought his video
彼のビデオを持ってきました
so everyone
だからみんな
inside
中身
to the point
ポイントへ
with different fluorescent proteins
さまざまな蛍光タンパク質を使用した
At present, fluorescent ornamental fish with two viewing modes, day and night, have been released
現在、昼と夜の2つの観察モードを備えた蛍光観賞魚が発売されています。
in the exploration of life
人生の探求において
Fluorescent fish not only have aquarium ornamental value
蛍光魚は観賞価値があるだけではありません
In academic research with the help of fluorescent fish
蛍光魚を使った学術研究
Come to understand the high-tech genetic engineering and gene transfer technology
ハイテク遺伝子工学と遺伝子導入技術を理解する
And explore and learn the mysteries of biotechnology
バイオテクノロジーの謎を探求して学びましょう
in drug research
薬物研究で
Using gene transfer technology to do drug research
遺伝子導入技術を利用した創薬研究
Can be used in biological therapy in the future
将来的には生物学的療法に使用できる
in medical research
医学研究において
Fluorescent fish can grow organs that glow in specific parts
蛍光魚は特定の部分が光る器官を成長させることができる
such as heart, liver
心臓、肝臓など
To observe the evolution of the disease and the use of drugs
病気の進行と薬物の使用を観察するため
is it effective
効果はありますか
Agricultural biotechnology is a hot new industry
農業バイオテクノロジーは注目の新産業です
Estimated four years later
推定4年後
The global agricultural production technology output value will reach 63 billion US dollars
世界の農業生産技術生産額は630億ドルに達する見込み
is a new trend in global agriculture
は世界の農業における新しいトレンドです
Taiwan is appreciating the difference in biotechnology
台湾はバイオテクノロジーの違いを高く評価している
Strong potential and advantages in industrial development
産業発展における大きな可能性と利点
in government support
政府の支援で
and the technical integration support of the Agricultural Biotechnology Industrialization Promotion Office
及び農業バイオ産業化推進室の技術融合支援
There will be huge business opportunities in the international market in the future
将来的には国際市場で大きなビジネスチャンスが生まれる
OK so let me explain
わかりました、それでは説明しましょう
Computing from lab research
実験室の研究から計算する
Indeed, the industry
まさに業界は、
They find new business opportunities to develop
彼らは新たなビジネスチャンスを見つけて開発します
But just now the vice president mentioned that
しかし今、副大統領がこう言いました。
If this fish is still the next generation
この魚がまだ次世代なら
If he buys it once, he won't buy it
一度買ったらもう買わない
It is more important to comply with biosafety issues
バイオセーフティの問題を遵守することがより重要です
Can not affect the ecology
生態系に影響を与えない
So for these unlucky platforms
したがって、これらの不運なプラットフォームについては、
Required for applications in genetically engineered and modified fish
遺伝子組み換え魚や遺伝子組み換え魚への応用に必要
And it is required by the regulations
そしてそれは規制によって義務付けられています
so gene transfer you run outside
だから遺伝子移入は外に出ろよ
Of course it will affect the ecology
生態系に影響を与えるのは当然
everyone knows
みんな知ってる
To be able to prevent it from affecting the environment and ecology
環境や生態系に影響を与えないようにするため
in case it escapes to wild conditions
野生状態に逃げた場合に備えて
so let's think
それで考えてみましょう
In this reproductive line of the flower chair system
このフラワーチェアシステムの生殖系統では
what's so special about fish
魚の何が特別なのか
When the fertilized eggs of fish start to wear flower chairs
魚の受精卵が花椅子を履き始める頃
it has this dead germ cell
この死んだ生殖細胞がある
germ cell precursor
生殖細胞前駆体
It is in the early stage of this flower chair
このフラワーチェアの初期段階です
Cells in these PGCs begin to differentiate
これらの PGC 内の細胞は分化を開始します
After these 20 days
この 20 日後
It differentiates and begins to resemble orgasm
それは分化し、オルガスムに似始めます
egg trough structure
卵槽構造
before the sex ropes
セックスロープの前に
It will be turned into a sperm and egg trough
精子と卵子の容器になります
egg trough
卵入れ
essence
エッセンス
is such a layered
とても階層的です
so can we try again
それでもう一度試してみませんか
Cells in PGC
PGC のセル
or soft cells
またはソフトセル
Expression of this specific gene using Molecular Biology
分子生物学を使用したこの特定の遺伝子の発現
If its cells can destroy it
細胞がそれを破壊できるとしたらどうなるでしょうか?
What about a fish like you it won't become non-hard
君みたいな魚はどうなるんだろう 硬くならないよ
But the female fish has to be able to get pregnant
しかし、メスの魚は妊娠できなければなりません
So this system is to be able to control the verbal
したがって、このシステムは言語を制御できるようにするためのものです。
This expression of this gene
この遺伝子のこの発現
So there is a kind of fish that can live forever
つまり、永遠に生きることができる魚がいるということです
Then do a specific treatment for the fish you want to sell
次に、売りたい魚に特別な処理を行います。
performance with enzymes
酵素によるパフォーマンス
or lighting method to deal with
または対処する照明方法
So we develop two methods
そこで 2 つの方法を開発します
So let's destroy its PCC
さあ、そのPCCを破壊してください
One is the method of blowing with enzymes
一つは酵素を吹き込む方法です。
we one this this
私たちはこれを一つにします
Make it not easy to dampen the beauty of the ring
リングの美しさを壊しにくいようにする
import into this glowfish
このグローフィッシュにインポートします
So this blowing with this enzyme
この酵素を使って吹くのです
What about making PCC cells
PCCセルを作る場合はどうなるか
it will kill it
それはそれを殺します
So there is no doubt about ejaculation or soft tide
だから射精か軟潮間違いなし
or we express luminal protein to it
または、それにルミナルタンパク質を発現させます
photo sensitive protein
光感受性タンパク質
it is irradiated with red light
赤い光が照射される
it will sharpen the free machine out
それは自由なマシンを研ぎ澄ますでしょう
also kills cells, soft cells
細胞や軟細胞も殺します
So the result of our approach like this
このようなアプローチの結果は
You can probably see the final result
おそらく最終結果がわかると思います
Elimination cyclase
除去シクラーゼ
to stimulate
刺激する
normal female soft
普通の女性ソフト
full of health
健康に満ちた
In fact, you can see one by one
実際に一つ一つ見てみると、
But after soaking in this machine
でもこのマシンに浸かった後は
cyclase
シクラーゼ
This is when Nitro Reductase comes into play
そこでニトロリダクターゼの出番です
Its metabolites let soft cells kill
その代謝物により軟細胞が死滅します
Therefore, soft frying will shrink and have no business force
そのため、柔らかく揚げると縮んでしまい営業力がありません。
Bright protein is the same
ブライトプロテインも同様
As a result, after the light is illuminated, after the red light is illuminated
その結果、ライト点灯後、赤色ライト点灯後
Shrink after soft frying
柔らかく揚げた後の縮み
This is a normal soft fry
こちらは普通のソフトフライです
So in this way it can be achieved
ということで、この方法で実現できるのです
Should not control
コントロールしてはいけない
However, we also cooperate with the industry for unsuitable technologies.
ただし、不適切な技術については業界と協力します。
Inappropriate off-coder and normal help
不適切なオフコーダーと通常のヘルプ
it is exactly the same
それは全く同じです
The color, body shape, vitality, health and sobriety are exactly the same
色も体型も元気も健康も節度も全く同じ
So we hope that technology like this in the industry can enter this market
したがって、業界のこのようなテクノロジーがこの市場に参入できることを願っています
Just mentioned why GMO is doing this biosafety assessment
GMO がこのバイオセーフティー評価を行う理由について先ほど述べました
Because one is concerns about environmental biosafety assessment
なぜなら、1つは環境の生物学的安全性評価に関する懸念だからです。
This is usually managed by the Council of Agriculture
通常、これは農業評議会によって管理されます
In foreign countries, plus the Environmental Protection Agency will govern this part
外国では、この部分を管理するために環境保護庁が追加される予定です
if you want to eat
食べたいなら
In the past, health was first and foremost the Ministry of Health and Welfare
かつては、健康は何よりもまず厚生省でした。
It is to manage this food safety
この食の安全を管理するのが
Both must be eligible for gold transfer
どちらもゴールド送金の対象となる必要があります
If you are an official
あなたが公務員であれば
As long as the Council of Agriculture and the Environmental Protection Agency can agree
農業評議会と環境保護庁が同意できる限り
If you want to use food, you still have to go through the food hygiene control of the Ministry of Health and Welfare
食品を使用する場合は、やはり厚生省の食品衛生管理を受けなければなりません。
Only after passing the test can it be used
テストに合格した場合のみ使用できます
Therefore, these studies must return to basic research
したがって、これらの研究は基礎研究に戻る必要があります。
Then our basic research
それから私たちの基礎研究
i feel full
満腹感がある
That is to say
つまり
Doing fish research always thinks
魚の研究をしていていつも思うのは、
Fish research is relatively backward
魚の研究は比較的遅れている
Behind the scenes of doing mouse studies
マウス研究の裏側
but 30 years ago
でも30年前
That's starting to see the zebrafish feature
ゼブラフィッシュの特徴が見え始めています
that can be used as a model animal
モデル動物として使用できる
So what about the zebrafish?
では、ゼブラフィッシュはどうでしょうか？
It has several characteristics
いくつかの特徴があります
It's its plastic egg
それはプラスチックの卵です
it is transparent
透明です
So it's an outside mouse again?
ということは、また社外マウスですか？
You can watch the change of its fluid at any time
流体の変化をいつでも観察できます
to the formation of organs
臓器の形成まで
So these two days the fish floated out
この二日間、魚が浮き出てきました
What about when the first day is over?
初日が終わったらどうなるでしょうか？
Happy to have some organs
臓器があれば嬉しい
Like the heart starts to drop
心が落ち込むように
Then its blood starts to flow and so on
その後、血液が循環し始めます。
these can see this
彼らはこれを見ることができます
what about the fish
魚はどうですか
It not only has a short melting time
溶ける時間が短いだけではありません
It can make it soft every week
毎週柔らかくすることができます
Every week can send soft
毎週ソフトを送信できます
200 to 400 pieces
200～400個
so what time
それで何時
Material
材料
I even extended this piece to primary and secondary education
この作品を初等中等教育にも拡張しました
You don't have to kill frogs before
その前にカエルを殺す必要はない
Then it's cruel to do these floral research, isn't it?
では、こうした花の研究をするのは残酷ですよね。
Now my name is Taiken Corporation
さて、私の名前は株式会社タイケンです
It was developed as a teaching material for primary and secondary schools
小・中学校向けの教材として開発されました。
Do it with this zebra chair
このゼブラチェアでやってみましょう
because we have to
なぜなら私たちはそうするつもりだから
Are zebra chairs the same as people?
ゼブラチェアも人間と同じですか？
This is a very important subject
これは非常に重要なテーマです
You want to be a model animal to study human diseases
人間の病気を研究するモデル動物になりたい
So in terms of cancer
これは癌に関する話です
Let's say it's human
それが人間だとしましょう
Pathology section of this different cancer
この異なるがんの病理学セクション
this is the zebra chair
これはゼブラチェアです
You can use this type of long way
このタイプの長距離を使用できます
Then it's almost very similar to
それから、それはほぼ次のようになります
or this clinical cell carcinoma
またはこの臨床細胞癌
Its structure is something like
その構造は次のようなものです
The pathological mechanism is also similar to
病理メカニズムも同様です
So the zebra chair was created to be an animal for human diseases
つまり、ゼブラチェアは人間の病気を治す動物として作られたのです
Some kind of disease, I think besides the disease of the lungs
肺の病気以外に何かの病気だと思います
Is it because it is a language that breathes with gills?
エラ呼吸する言語だからでしょうか？
Other probably you see these physical diseases
他にもおそらく次のような身体疾患が見られるでしょう
including mental illness or toxicity
精神疾患や中毒を含む
Dr. Ma can provide us with good
馬を助ける医師は私たちに良いものを提供してくれる
The material of this study so the new technology of these studies
この研究の材料であるため、これらの研究の新技術
Functional research and development have also constructed a very complete
機能的な研究開発も非常に完成度の高い製品を構築しました。
Academia Sinica takes the lead in developing different technologies in China
中央研究院が中国でさまざまな技術開発を主導
Reporting to you means that Congress will support it.
あなたに報告するということは、議会がそれを支持することを意味します。
Our Academia Sinica built a core facility for horse medicine
私たちの中央研究院は馬医学の中核施設を建設しました
So we use the core of Academia Sinica
そこで私たちは中央研究院の中核を利用します。
Like a laboratory in Taiwan that helps horse medicine do research
馬医学の研究を支援する台湾の研究所のようなもの
We counted 110
110を数えました
that's quite a lot
それはかなり多いです
We feel that there are so many research teams like this in Taiwan
台湾にはこのような研究チームがたくさんあると感じます
is it possible
出来ますか
It can be used to present our Taiwan application on the neighbor’s house
隣の家に台湾の申請書を提示するのに使用できます
Is that actually
本当にあるんですか
In fact there is already this system
実はこの制度はすでにあります
Intervention as a drug screen using zebrafish
ゼブラフィッシュを用いた薬物スクリーニングとしての介入
Then these foreign laboratories
それから、これらの外国の研究所は、
Or the pharmaceutical company has already done
あるいは製薬会社がすでに行っている
There is no way this small Taiwanese kitchen can do it
この小さな台湾のキッチンにそれができるわけがない
This high-throughput screening
このハイスループットスクリーニング
Usually, our drug screening is to use cells to screen
通常、私たちの薬物スクリーニングは細胞を使用してスクリーニングします。
its efficacy or toxicity test
その有効性または毒性試験
Then jump to the mouse experiment
次に、マウスの実験に進みます
But the cost of experimenting with this intermediate mouse is very high
しかし、この中間マウスの実験コストは非常に高くなります
And the requirements for animal support are also very strict.
そして動物支援の要件も非常に厳しいです。
So now I have a new idea
そこで今、新しいアイデアを思いつきました
from cell culture screening
細胞培養スクリーニングから
Before entering the experimental animal screening of mice
マウスの実験動物スクリーニングに入る前に
can help barbarian fish can intervene
野蛮な魚を助けることができる 介入することができる
Speed ​​up and reduce costs
スピードアップとコスト削減
So let’s talk about the object of this screening
それでは今回の上映会の目的についてお話しましょう
Say from 1000 you win 1000 screenings
1000 回から 1000 回の上映に当選するとします
You can help the fish
魚を助けることができる
you take 100 tests
あなたは100回のテストを受けます
Among them, the best 12 need compounds
その中でベスト 12 の必要な化合物
Only after entering the system of Oster
オスター星系に入ってからのみ
so the system
それでシステムは
Zebra Doctor's screening system has entered such a stage
Zebra Doctorのスクリーニングシステムはそんな段階に突入しました
So a couple of examples
いくつかの例を示します
one is
一つは
this suppression
この抑圧
active ink
アクティブインクなど
Talk to Zai about this medicine
この薬についてザイと話す
this chemical
この化学物質
this is
これは
it has zebra doctor pattern
ゼブラドクターパターンがあります
It is similar to the main plug of our blood vessels
私たちの血管の幹栓に似ています
So the blood can't get out
血が外に出ないので
After soaking it with this medicine, the blood cleared
この薬に浸すと血液がきれいになりました
So this color means the blood vessels are circulating
つまり、この色は血管が循環していることを意味します
This means that such a drug
つまり、そのような薬は、
It is indeed possible to re-live the situation that Mo Zai said actively
墨載が積極的に言った状況を再現することは確かに可能です
the second is
2番目は
particle means
粒子の意味
This medicine it's a Tyrotin-Kan's inhibitor
この薬はチロチンカン阻害剤です
That's actually a medicine
あれ実は薬なんです
it can suppress this
これを抑制できる
anti-angiogenesis
抗血管新生
Because of cancer you also want blood vessels not to regenerate
がんのせいで血管が再生しないようにしたい
Tissue from cancer cells shrinks
がん細胞の組織が縮小する
So this is a normal vessel aorta
これは正常な血管の大動脈です
Then the branching vessels
その後、血管が分岐します
After getting this medicine in
この薬を入れてから
Some blood vessels are different
一部の血管が異なります
Said that this can be directly analyzed by image
これは画像から直接解析できるとのこと
Let's see if the medicine works
薬が効くかどうか見てみましょう
This is an in vivo effect that can be observed with zebrafish
これはゼブラフィッシュで観察できる生体内効果です
So like this I'm giving two examples
このように 2 つの例を示します
So many automated systems have been developed
非常に多くの自動化システムが開発されています
then i will say too fast
それでは早口で言ってしまいます
Then our Sense is more interested in the liver
その場合、私たちの感覚は肝臓により興味を持ちます
Because the flower chair of Urman's liver is made by very few people
ウルマンの肝臓の花椅子はごく少数の人が作っているので
in fish
在魚類
The second one is related to our Taiwan, especially the liver disease in Taiwan
2つ目は私たちの台湾、特に台湾の肝臓病に関するものです。
Aspects of the liver can be linked
肝臓の側面は関連している可能性があります
So we're going to do live liver
ということでライブ肝をやります
Suspicion of the liver Before we have to find a professional liver
肝臓の疑い 肝臓の専門家を見つける前に
priming mass
プライミングマス
So the genetic modification on our side
つまり、私たちの側の遺伝子組み換えは
The liver is indeed only the liver has pronunciation light
肝臓は確かに肝臓だけが発音が軽いです
This way we can directly observe changes in the liver
これにより、肝臓の変化を直接観察できるようになります。
Is it sick or not? The suspected condition is normal or not.
病気ですか? 疑わしい状態は正常ですか?
we can discuss it
私たちはそれについて話し合うことができます
If combined with human liver disease
ヒトの肝疾患を合併した場合
We know that if it's a viral liver disease
それがウイルス性肝疾患であることはわかっています
Liver that has undergone thick liver and thin liver
厚い肝臓と薄い肝臓を経た肝臓
Liver disease can cause fatty liver
肝臓病は脂肪肝を引き起こす可能性があります
hepatitis liver fibrosis
肝炎、肝線維症
If unlucky, it will become cirrhosis
運が悪ければ肝硬変になる
Liver cancer
肝臓がん
Is the zebra doctor in these processes disadvantaged?
これらのプロセスにおいてシマウマ博士は不利な立場にあるのでしょうか?
we will establish such a mechanism
そういう仕組みを確立していきます
Indeed we put this
確かにこれを入れました
Antigen protein of blood-sucking liver refining or nosebleed liver refining
吸血肝臓または鼻血肝臓の抗原タンパク質
go to zebrafish
ゼブラフィッシュに行く
when to observe
いつ観察するか
Here's what happened to the mouse's liver cancer incarnation
マウスの肝臓がんの化身に何が起こったかは次のとおりです
from normal
普通から
hepatic fibrosis
肝線維症
Then adenoma tumor and liver cancer
次に腺腫腫瘍と肝がん
About 68 weeks, about one year and five months
約68週間、約1年5ヶ月
The zebrafish system we specifically built
私たちが特別に構築したゼブラフィッシュ システム
If it is treated with carcinogenic TAA chemical drugs
発がん性のあるTAA化学薬品で治療された場合
It is 12 weeks, about three months will produce this ACC
このACCの製作には12週間、約3ヶ月かかります
If you want to turn straight to this ACV
この ACV に直接アクセスしたい場合は、
It is the core protein refined by blood-sucking liver
吸血肝臓によって精製されるコアタンパク質です
About 6 weeks to 8 weeks to see the changes in the organization with ACC
6週間から8週間程度で組織の変化がACCでわかる
So the time is shortened a lot
なので時間はかなり短縮されます
This facilitates our discussion as disease
これにより、病気としての議論が容易になります
So we also observe
それで私たちも観察します
It's the virus that we use to separate the liver from the liver
肝臓と肝臓を分離するために使用されるウイルスです
HBX and HCP are transferred until the zebrafish performs
HBX と HCP はゼブラフィッシュが行動するまで移送されます。
We saw that its pathological section showed short tube abnormalities
病理断面には短管異常が見られました
Then the short pipe anomaly
そして、この短いパイプの異常
ICC between us and human
私たちと人間の間のICC
This is what we call this short-to-carcinoma ICC in the liver
これは、肝臓におけるこの短発がん性 ICC と呼ばれるものです。
its unusually short structure
異常に短い構造
the pathological conditions are quite similar
病理学的状態は非常に似ています
So let's go over the disease pattern study
それでは、疾患パターン研究を見てみましょう
We are very interested in exploring these mechanisms
私たちはこれらのメカニズムの探索に非常に興味を持っています
When I have a chance, I will report the details to you again.
機会がありましたら、また詳細をご報告させていただきます。
In addition, we have
さらに、
because our digestive tract
なぜなら私たちの消化管は
So long that we actually wanted to study
私たちが本当に勉強したいと思っていたほど長い間
For example, it can be linked to colorectal cancer
たとえば、結腸直腸がんに関連する可能性があります。
That research is moving bowel cancer
その研究は大腸がんを動かしています
We can make this gut only bonus silver
このガットだけボーナスシルバーにできます
we use kongfokou
私たちは孔福口を使います
This is what the Chinese call Kong Fokou
これを中国人はコン・フォーコウと呼んでいます
highway treat
高速道路のご褒美
This risky technique taught by industry
業界が教えるこの危険なテクニック
Then let's crosscut its long structure
それでは、その長い構造を横断的に見てみましょう
So we can see the long tube from different parts
長いチューブをさまざまな部分から見ることができます
It is very uniform and can express red and silver light
非常に均一で赤や銀の光を表現できます
So the fish if it has been processed
魚が加工されている場合
or genetic changes
または遺伝子の変化
If there is a tumor on the long road
長い道のりに腫瘍があったら
These changes are coming
こういった変化がやってくる
So we can do these experimental studies
したがって、これらの実験研究を行うことができます
This is the platform we hope to be able to express with the light of the digestive organs
消化器の光で表現したいプラットフォームです
Studying the Mechanism from Digestion to Formation
消化から形成までの仕組みを解明
we pass this
私たちはこれを渡します
So we have built this zebrafish
そこで私たちはこのゼブラフィッシュを作りました
It is red and silver light
赤と銀の光です
Dry Tibet is green and silver light
乾いたチベットは緑と銀の光です
the same fish again
また同じ魚
so we can study their two different organs
それで私たちは彼らの 2 つの異なる器官を研究することができます
The relationship between interaction and disease
相互作用と病気の関係
I'll finish speaking in about ten minutes, okay?
10分ほどで話し終えます、いいですか？
We will then
それでは、
then industrial innovation
それから産業革新
this is the government
これが政府です
then please let me take charge of this project
それでは私にこのプロジェクトを担当させてください
the adoption of agricultural biotechnology
農業バイオテクノロジーの導入
Promote programs wishing to bring academic research
学術研究をもたらすプログラムを推進する
Can be imported into the industry
業界に輸入できる
The needs of industry can allow academia to interact
産業界のニーズにより、学界の交流が可能になる
So this plan starts from an innovative productization platform
この計画は革新的な製品化プラットフォームから始まります
We are doing both with commoditization
コモディティ化と両方を行っています
We, the Chinese and British communities, are responsible
私たち中国人と英国人コミュニティには責任があります
There are various parts to come together to participate
参加するにはさまざまな部分があります
We have a calibration focus in aquatic products
当社は水産物の校正に重点を置いています
Just mentioned again and again is
先ほども何度も言いましたが、
Grouper, Taiwan sea bream, ornamental fish and shrimp are our focus
ハタ、タイダイ、観賞魚、エビが中心です
So there are a lot of successful
だから成功者もたくさんいる
Through plan matchmaking and plan transfer
プランマッチメイキングとプラン移行により
There are many successful cases to carry out
実践して成功した事例も多数あります
The grouper industry
ハタ産業
There is also the industry chain of sea bream
鯛の産業チェーンもある
Industrial chain of ornamental fish
観賞魚の産業チェーン
There are already successful companies in the shrimp industry chain
エビ産業チェーンにはすでに成功している企業がある
or start making money
またはお金を稼ぎ始めます
So I'll let it pass quickly on my side
だから私はそれを私の側で早く過ぎさせます
So, for example, this one just talked about molecular markers
たとえば、これは分子マーカーについて話したばかりです
Just mentioned there are several techniques to perform
実行するにはいくつかのテクニックがあると述べました
Like in addition to the research results of our laboratory
当研究室の研究成果に加えて
we also see
私たちも見ています
We have combined one of Taiwan's largest companies that export products
台湾最大手の製品輸出会社と提携しました。
And Taiwan is number one and number two
そして台湾は1位と2位です
Belonging to all feed companies
すべての飼料会社に所属
to bring them together
それらを一つにまとめるために
A company, a feed company, let it raise fish
会社、飼料会社、魚を育てさせてください
Then this accompanying product company
それからこの付随製品会社
It will be processed and exported to the world
加工されて世界に輸出される
Therefore, Taiwan Eagle can be established to internationalize its products
したがって、製品を国際化するために台湾イーグルを設立することができます
You can learn about companies like this
このような企業について知ることができます
Big grower he told me
偉大な栽培者である彼は私にこう言いました
He employs more than 1,000 people abroad
彼は海外で1,000人以上を雇用している
The talents we train in Taiwan are no better than others
私たちが台湾で育成した人材は他の人材と比べても遜色ありません
So it can be seen how big the industry they see
彼らが見ている業界がどれほど大きいかがわかります
The following aspect has this technique from detecting
次のアスペクトには、検出からのこのテクニックがあります。
The disease agrees that he is also close
病気も彼が近いことに同意します
as well as with Rakyo Marine, which makes the instruments.
楽器を製造するRakyo Marineも同様です。
Nazang Nanya did very well
ナザン・ナーニャはとても上手でした
I just talked about the technology that shouldn't be
あってはならないテクノロジーについてお話しました。
our continuous development
私たちの継続的な発展
This is the technology of the fluorescent chair
これが蛍光椅子の技術です
So let's talk about this technology in particular.
それでは、特にこのテクノロジーについて話しましょう。
Russian Academy of Sciences
ロシア科学アカデミー
In the past few years, the Chinese Academy has also booked a cooperative project
過去数年間、中国アカデミーも協力プロジェクトを予約しました
he saw and said
彼は見て言った
My deep sea club wants to build a marine museum
私の深海クラブは海洋博物館を建設したいと考えています
In particular, Taiwan's ornamental instruments will be displayed
特に台湾の装飾楽器が展示されます。
Because seeing Taiwan's innovative technology
台湾の革新的な技術を見てから
Vaccines Against Emergencies
緊急事態に対するワクチン
Detection Reagent
検出試薬
This technology can use immune weight gain as a data additive
このテクノロジーは、免疫による体重増加をデータ付加物として使用できます。
Let's take on this again to talk about his development
彼の成長についてもう一度話しましょう
He is only the five companies involved in this plan
この計画に参加しているのは彼だけの 5 社です
we count for him
私たちは彼のために数えます
His transfer income has exceeded 50 million
移籍収入は5000万を超えた
So it can create a lot of output value
したがって、多くの出力価値を生み出すことができます
So we hope that such technology can be biased to the
したがって、そのようなテクノロジーが次のようなことに偏ることができることを願っています。
Can be applied in markets all over the world
世界中の市場で応用可能
augmentation is data
拡張はデータです
Transfer and processing
調供加工
DHA is cultured in the early column
初期カラムでDHAを培養
This is also the technology achieved by Weidan Company
これも魏丹社が実現した技術です
it has been certified
それは認定されました
Many foreign manufacturers have come to Weidan to say
多くの外国メーカーが渭丹に来てこう言いました。
You are producing DHA very well
DHAを上手に生成していますね
Cultivated and extracted from the early column
初期のコラムから培養および抽出
So it has become an industry
それで産業になった
Collagen
コラーゲン
is my past student
私の過去の生徒です
his own company
彼自身の会社
he does diabetic couple
彼は糖尿病夫婦です
to apply the growth of entertainment thus
エンターテイメントの成長をこのように応用する
Can be used as a couple with diabetes
糖尿病のあるカップルでも利用可能
I have entered clinical trials
臨床試験に参加しました
further
さらに遠く
turn into medicine
薬に変わる
We also work with this company
私たちもこの会社と提携しています
Never Too Much Neighbors
隣人が多すぎることはありません
can be extracted
抽出できる
Can make successful angle mold
アングルモールドを成功させることができる
What about this technique?
このテクニックはどうでしょうか？
we are training him
私たちは彼を訓練しています
We want to raise more than 3 kg of five countries fish
5ヶ国の魚を3kg以上育てたい
The scales are over and we've seen it
スケールは終わった、そして我々はそれを見た
Then they plan to compete with Germany this year
そして今年はドイツと対戦する予定だ
Clinical trials at the Faculty of Medicine of the University of Cologne
ケルン大学医学部における臨床試験
Then we hope that if this works out,
それで、これがうまくいけば、
to human health
人間の健康に
This should be of great help
これは大いに役立つはずです
So you can't imagine saying
だからあなたはこう言うことは想像できない
How can fish things be used by people?
魚のものをどうやって人に使ってもらえるのか？
That's because of the collagen in fish scales
それは魚の鱗に含まれるコラーゲンのおかげです
it is most like a person
それは最も人に似ています
The first, the second, fish and man
最初と二番目の魚と人間
it has no common infectious disease
一般的な感染症はありません
It's a virus
ウイルスです
So its safety is higher than other animal sources
そのため、他の動物由来のものよりも安全性が高いです
So they have this consideration
そこで彼らはこのような考慮をしているのです
Then as cosmetics etc.
あとは化粧品などとして。
The third is our aquatic products
3つ目は水産物です。
We often go abroad
私たちはよく海外に行きます
Although the government has various regulations
政府は様々な規制を設けていますが、
We have production and sales experience
製造・販売実績がございます
There is also CAS certification
CAS認証も取得しています
Some
いくつかの
Only then can ordinary people and consumers be able to use it domestically
そうして初めて国内で一般の人や消費者が使えるようになるのです。
But there are different certifications in foreign countries
ただし、海外ではさまざまな認証が存在します
For example, the European Union has ASC certification
たとえば、欧州連合には ASC 認証があります。
North America is also this Europe and the United States, it has its BAP certification
北米も欧州や米国と同様にBAP認証を取得しています。
Then our certification is still not up to their certification standards
その場合、私たちの認証はまだ認証基準に達していません
Japan has JAS certification
日本にはJAS認証がある
Therefore, food safety certification standards in these countries have various certification standards
したがって、これらの国の食品安全認証基準にはさまざまな認証基準があります。
So our Taiwan certification in the past is that this grows fast
つまり、当社の過去の台湾認証は、急速に成長しているということです。
Then the cost is low, and this harmless substance can be used.
そうすればコストも安く、この無害な物質を使用することができます。
But the international standard it requires is higher
しかし、要求される国際基準はさらに高い
So how to comply with international certification is very important
したがって、国際認証にどのように準拠するかが非常に重要です
Another one is for the environment of the earth and for the welfare of animals
もう一つは地球環境と動物の福祉のためです
for...
ために...
social stability
社会の安定
International farming new crown
國際養殖新冠
Not just Yangyi itself
楊儀そのものだけではない
Certification of our grooming
当社のグルーミング認証
Have you entered social responsibility
社会的責任を果たしていますか
Have you paid attention to the health of the fracture?
骨折の状態に注意を払いましたか？
with his well being
彼の健康とともに
Have you met the food safety requirements
食品安全要件を満たしていますか
Have you caused damage to the environment
環境に損害を与えましたか
Do you meet the standards of the green industry
グリーン産業の基準を満たしていますか
Wait for these certifications to be added one by one
これらの認定が 1 つずつ追加されるまで待ちます
So we hope that Taiwan's industry
したがって、台湾の産業が発展することを願っています。
Can have an international perspective
国際的な視野を持てる
In order to maintain the invincible position of interests
利益の無敵の地位を維持するために
Just mentioned these different national certifications
これらのさまざまな国家資格について言及しました
The strictest ones seem to be the European and American markets
最も厳しいのはヨーロッパとアメリカの市場のようです
So we need to get these recognitions
したがって、これらの認識を得る必要があります
our chance is there
私たちのチャンスはそこにある
Finally, because of the proposed marine biotechnology
最後に、海洋バイオテクノロジーの提案により、
Research on the development of industry for us in Taiwan
台湾における研究産業の発展
Taiwan's future is very important
台湾の将来は非常に重要です
So our colleagues in many domestic academic circles
国内の多くの学界の私たちの同僚
under active efforts
積極的な取り組み中
We established the Taiwan Society of Marine Biotechnology the year before last
一昨年、台湾海洋バイオテクノロジー学会を設立しました。
So this society
だからこの社会は
We did what we learned to do
私たちはやるべきことを学んだことをやった
We are also willing to go to the Fisheries Vocational School
水産専門学校にも進学したいです
to his teacher
彼の先生に
Bring them the development of new technologies in marine biotechnology
海洋バイオテクノロジーの新技術の開発を彼らにもたらす
I also hope that their students can participate in this kind of event
生徒たちにもこのようなイベントに参加してもらいたいと思っています
laboratory work
実験室での仕事
We also extend to the education of high school vocational education
高等学校の職業教育まで幅広く展開します
We will also host the 10th Asia-Pacific Marine Biotechnology Conference in May this year
今年5月には第10回アジア太平洋海洋バイオテクノロジー会議も開催します。
They have suggested that Taiwan has such a foundation
彼らは台湾にはそのような基盤があると示唆した
so i take the responsibility
だから私が責任を負います
with the domestic academic circles
国内学会との連携
to cooperate
協力する
So our positioning is this theme
つまり、私たちのポジショニングはこのテーマです
not only science
科学だけでなく
Our new challenges to food, medicine, energy and the environment
食料、医療、エネルギー、環境への新たな挑戦
is the subject of our discussion
それは私たちの議論の主題です
Then in the end, we have to deal with our Taiwan
そして最終的には台湾と向き合わなければなりません
What is the prospect of the next life
次の人生の展望は何ですか
So
それで
run back
逃げる
Sorry
ごめん
we run back
私たちは走って戻ります
because of time
時間のせいで
I hope this is OK
これで大丈夫だといいのですが
so the first
それで最初の
Although we are with what we eat every day
毎日食べるものと一緒なのに
eat well
よく食べる
eat healthy
健康的に食べる
This is very important
これはとても重要です
so i often say
だから私はよく言います
we eat delicious food
私たちはおいしいものを食べます
Or delicious aquatic products
またはおいしい水産物
all feel very happy
みんなとても幸せを感じています
People of this generation are better than those of 50 years ago
この世代の人々は50年前の人々より優れています
we are the same
我々は同じだ
people who only live in Taiwan
台湾にしか住んでいない人
So happy
とても幸せ
too much, right?
多すぎますよね？
you see it so
そう見えますか
Look at this from snapper, snapper fillet, eel
鯛・鯛の切り身・うなぎから見る
right this eel
そう、この鰻
this perch this oyster this mullet roe
このスズキ このカキ このカラスミ
Grass Shrimp Grouper Milkfish
グラスシュリンプ ハタサバヒー
soup mound toad toad
スープマウンド ヒキガエル ヒキガエル
everything, right?
すべてですよね？
very happy very happy
非常幸福 非常幸福
Some people used to eat these
これを食べていた人もいました
So our last hope is
だから私たちの最後の希望は
our marine living resources
私たちの海洋生物資源
We must explore through research
研究を通じて探求しなければなりません
and understand it
そしてそれを理解する
find it this feature
この機能を見つけてください
find its mechanism
そのメカニズムを見つける
So use biotechnology
そこでバイオテクノロジーを活用する
sustainable development of marine biological resources
海洋生物資源の持続可能な開発
we can achieve this
私たちはこれを達成できます
We humans live on this earth
私たち人間はこの地球上で生きています
Only then can it be very evil
そうして初めて、それは非常に邪悪なものになることができます
There are conditions for this development
この発展には条件がある
To maintain the food and health of such a large population
これほど多くの人々の食糧と健康を維持するために
Well this wishes all his distinguished guests
さて、これは彼の著名なゲスト全員の願いです
Then everyone is healthy and happy
そうすればみんなが健康で幸せになります
so auspicious
とても縁起が良い
Then we hope that our ocean Taiwan
そして、私たちの海が台湾であることを願っています。
just active perpetual
ただアクティブな永続的
Then I'll come here with you all to make a conclusion.
それから私は皆さんと一緒にここに来て結論を出します。
thank you all
皆さん、ありがとうございました
We are very grateful to researcher Wu Teping
研究者のウー・テピン氏に深く感謝します。
Secretary-General Wu gave us this brilliant speech
呉事務総長が素晴らしいスピーチをしてくれました
There is a section on this one about aquatic biotechnology
これには水生バイオテクノロジーに関するセクションがあります
That's because the content is quite substantial
内容がかなり濃いので
so maybe some of you in the audience
もしかしたら聴衆の中の何人かは
the audience is not very clear
聴衆はあまり明確ではありません
so if there are some problems
それで、何か問題があれば
we can ask
私たちは尋ねることができます
that if there is
それがあれば
please raise your hand
手を挙げてください
And then here's the microphone press the green part
そして、これがマイクの緑色の部分を押します
this gentleman please
この紳士、お願いします
Thanks
ありがとう
Teacher Wu's very wonderful speech
ウー先生のとても素晴らしいスピーチ
There was a place that was very impressive just now
今とても印象に残っている場所がありました
That is, Mr. Wu is not just studying
つまり、呉さんはただ勉強しているだけではないのです。
Moreover, it is also noted that the business needs to protect and obtain
さらに、企業は保護し、取得する必要があることにも注意してください。
So there is research on this issue of not shipping politics
政治を発信しないというこの問題についての研究があります
but i thought of saying
でも言おうと思った
we except this
私たちはこれを除いて
But besides this technology, Mr. Wu
しかし、このテクノロジーのほかに、ウー氏は
There are also fluorescent fish
蛍光魚もいるよ
Do cornea again
もう一度角膜をやります
and nutritious
そして栄養価の高い
anti-disease
抗病気
immune to disease
病気に対する免疫
many techniques
多くのテクニック
None of these technologies seem to
これらのテクノロジーはどれもそうではないようです
Protect it like Buyunzheng
芭雲正のように守ってください
That is to say
つまり
We sell light fish abroad
海外でもライトフィッシュを販売しております
people can't reproduce
人は再現できない
buy from us again
もう一度私たちから購入してください
But the recent corneal technology
しかし、最近の角膜技術は
anti-disease technology
抗病気技術
anticancer technology
抗癌技術
anti virus technology
ウイルス対策技術
It seems that there is no protection
保護は無いようです
I just want to ask
ただ聞きたいのですが
we taiwan
私たち台湾
Even Mr. Wu's own technology
呉氏独自の技術も
The protection against the outflow of technology
技術流出に対する保護
is there any way
何か方法はありますか
or measures
または対策
Thanks
ありがとう
The question we ask is that
私たちが尋ねる質問は、
How to protect the technology we develop
私たちが開発したテクノロジーを保護する方法
Our biggest concern is exodus
私たちの最大の懸念は国外流出です
good technique good seed outflow
良い技術 良い種子流出
I can't come back after going out
出かけたら戻れない
Instead, it arrived in Taiwan, right?
代わりに台湾に到着しましたね。
What about this situation?
この状況はどうでしょうか？
Agriculture, forestry, fishery and animal husbandry have all happened
農業、林業、漁業、畜産はすべて起こっています
then this so
じゃあこれで
one is to say
一つは言うことです
what about these technologies
これらのテクノロジーはどうですか
If able to have patent protection
特許保護を受けることができる場合
Then we all encourage the industry to say
それから私たちは皆、業界にこう言うよう奨励します。
Only those with patent protection will give priority to doing calculations
特許で保護されているものだけがコンピューティングを優先する
So this technique
そこでこのテクニック
after it turns around
振り返った後
What about the technology of its industry?
その業界のテクノロジーについてはどうですか?
not easy to lose
失うのは簡単ではない
just not easy
ただ簡単ではない
People may be able to counterfeit
人間は偽造できるかもしれない
But what about our cooperation in Taiwan?
しかし、台湾における私たちの協力はどうでしょうか？
not a one time cooperation
一度きりの協力ではない
It is attribute forward cooperation
属性フォワード連携です
So work with the industry
だから業界と協力して
industry-leading technology
業界をリードするテクノロジー
So we are standing here
だから私たちはここに立っている
Foundations for Pleasant Research
楽しい研究の基盤
come work with it
さあ、それで働きましょう
So part of the industry
つまり業界の一部
We all let the industry pay attention to the development of the district
業界全体が地区の発展に注目できるようにします
So it is very important to obtain a patent
したがって、特許を取得することは非常に重要です
The second is to say that the past patents are all patents
2つ目は、過去の特許はすべて特許であるということです。
So for example, will you predict
それで、たとえば、予測しますか
But your detection of the disease, the development of a disease vaccine
しかし、病気の発見、病気のワクチンの開発
or additives to test materials, etc.
または試験材料への添加物など。
We hope that these key technologies will be integrated
これらの主要なテクノロジーが統合されることを期待しています
For example, for this Shiban chair
例えばこのシバンチェアの場合
We start from the detection of pre-total disease
私たちは未病の発見から始めます
then vaccine development
それからワクチン開発
Then special samples
続いてスペシャルサンプル
and breeding environment
そして飼育環境も
We need to integrate several technologies together
いくつかのテクノロジーを統合する必要がある
system integration
システム統合
So if you are just a technical vent
つまり、あなたが単なる技術的な表現者である場合は、
He can't compete with Taiwan abroad
海外では台湾と太刀打ちできない
Therefore, the integration of technology is important for the protection of our Taiwan technology
したがって、技術の統合は台湾の技術を保護するために重要です。
is very important
はとても重要です
So this piece must become
したがって、この作品はこうなるに違いありません
teamwork
チームワーク
So we just mentioned a few examples
いくつかの例を挙げました
It was promoted in our fancy office
それは私たちの豪華なオフィスで宣伝されました
For example, Dachangcheng and Jiafeng
たとえば、大長城と嘉峰です。
These are two companies with different business objectives
これら 2 つの会社は異なるビジネス目標を持っています
It has different technical expertise
さまざまな技術的専門知識を持っています
plus academia collaboration
プラス学術連携
Although it is tied together
繋がっているのに
So if this is the case
したがって、これが事実であれば
You say my Jiafeng this part
あなたは私の嘉峰のこの部分を言います
I want to go out and get it
外に出て取りに行きたい
The part about adopting an aunt does not have a source of good aunts
叔母を養子にするという部分には、良い叔母に関する情報源がありません
It can't be taken away, right?
奪うことはできないですよね？
the same situation
同じ状況
Therefore, it is very important to be able to integrate technology
したがって、テクノロジーを統合できることが非常に重要です
So we have to break through the past and say we fight alone
だから私たちは過去を打ち破って、一人で戦うと言わなければなりません
In the past, if Taiwan went out alone, there would be no
かつて、台湾が単独で出動すれば、
Now it's time to integrate the technology
今こそテクノロジーを統合する時です
not easy to lose
失うのは簡単ではない
And it will be sustainable in Taiwan
そしてそれは台湾でも持続可能になるでしょう
this is my personal opinion
これは私の個人的な意見です
how does it look
どのように見えますか
this side in front
手前のこちら側
Okay, then there's that one
わかりました、それならそれがあります
Teacher Qiao Qiu
チャオ・チウ先生
ask the teacher
先生に尋ねる
to the one just mentioned
先ほど挙げたものに
Ultra-masculine nothing too much interest
超男性的であまり興味がありません
Then, since this is gray, adjust it naturally
あとはグレーなので自然に調整します
bred by the conditions
条件によって育てられる
How to breed this little female bird
この小さなメスの鳥を繁殖させる方法
And that is to say, from a traditional biological point of view
つまり、伝統的な生物学的観点から言えば、
That is to say, the performance-related body is not as good as X can be involved in the body.
つまり、パフォーマンス関連のボディは、X がボディに関与できるほど優れていません。
won't grow up or die
成長することも死ぬこともない
How to overcome this problem
この問題を克服する方法
In other words, this technology is in addition to no abalone
つまり、この技術はアワビに加えて、
Is there another one that can be used as well?
他に同様に使用できるものはありますか?
Thanks
ありがとう
ok i'll go back to zai
はい、ザイに戻ります
can you go back quickly
早く戻ってもらえますか
That's the superhero line
それはスーパーヒーローのラインです
Yes yes X Y that one
はいはいXYあれ
what about this
これはどうですか
it this
それこの
Thanks
ありがとう
This means that all male fish are used to mate here.
これは、すべての雄魚がここで交尾するために使用されることを意味します。
The male fish thus becomes pseudo-maternal
したがって、雄の魚は擬似的な母性を持ちます。
That means your XY fish is male, right?
ということは、あなたのXYの魚はオスということですね？
It can use this sex hormone, type X to feed it
この性ホルモン、タイプ X を使用して栄養を与えることができます
So it turns into a warm tide, not just a warm tide
だからただの暖かい潮ではなく暖かい潮になる
So it's transgender, transgender fish
つまり、それはトランスジェンダー、トランスジェンダーの魚です
So it's transgender, but it's an XY chromosome
つまり、トランスジェンダーですが、XY染色体です
But it's sexual, it can be soft, there's sperm on this side
でもそれは性的で、柔らかくてもいいし、こちら側には精子がある
So after it was born, after it was bred
だから、生まれた後、育てられた後、
XY and XX are not half and half
XYとXXは半々ではない
Only 25% of XX, 75% of male
XX ではわずか 25%、男性では 75%
XY is still 50%, but YY is 1⁴
XY はまだ 50% ですが、YY は 1⁴
So this is hypermale, so males will be 75%
これはハイパー男性なので、男性が 75% になります
So Chaoxiong uses it like this
チャオションはこのように使います
In this way, I became this YY and cultivated it like this
こうしてこのYYとなり、こうして育てられました
but it only has one generation
しかし、それは1世代しかありません
That's why we have to return to the previous one every time.
そのため、毎回前に戻る必要があります。
So this is just for breeding purposes
つまり、これは繁殖目的だけです
In turn, I just mentioned mullet roe
翻って、さっきカラスミのことを言いましたが、
Then you want pee, right?
じゃあおしっこが欲しいですよね？
So it is to make it turn bears into males
クマを雄に変えるためです
So the whole teeth are raised by males
そのため、歯全体が男性によって持ち上げられます。
The tortoise is feeding the bear
亀が熊に餌をあげている
So this breeding
それでこの繁殖
In fact, these technologies in Taiwan were developed more than 20 years ago.
実際、これらの技術は台湾で 20 年以上前に開発されました。
Well it starts a bit like Try and error doing
まあ、それはトライアンドエラーのような感じで始まります
Then slowly we will enter the import comparison
それからゆっくりと輸入比較に入ります
Biotechnology methods can identify
バイオテクノロジー手法で特定できるのは、
Well wait these can be done
まあ待ってください、これらはできるでしょう
am i currently
私は今ですか？
Good Mr. Qiu
良いです、邱さん
Secretary-General Wu, thank you for your one-page research on Taiwan
呉事務総長、台湾に関する1ページにわたる調査をありがとうございました
communism in development
発展中の共産主義
Thank you for giving us this opportunity
この機会を与えていただきありがとうございます
Let's think about this question of fisheries development
漁業開発に関するこの問題について考えてみましょう
i have two questions
質問が2つあります
The first is how do we define Taiwan eagle heels?
まず、台湾のカービングヒールをどのように定義するかということです。
Wu Guoyu
呉国宇
I think a lot of people want to know
知りたい人も多いと思います
Myself I just said Wu Guoyu
私自身、今呉国宇と言ったところです
The second one is when we are studying
2つ目は勉強しているときです
while doing scientific research
科学研究をしながら
We also understand
私たちも理解しています
We are going to talk about the sustainable development of fishery resources
水産資源の持続可能な発展についてお話します。
can't leave the environment
環境から離れることができない
But I have been in the US for about ten years
しかし、私は約10年間アメリカに住んでいます
Then back to Taiwan I saw
それから台湾に戻って私は見ました
Because my family lives next to Zhuowei Creek
私の家族は卓威渓の隣に住んでいるからです
Then I saw the whole side of Zhuowei Creek
それから私は卓威渓の全体を見ました
It turns out that the one that can be used for fish breeding
魚の飼育に使えることが判明
the tide environment
潮汐環境
has been replaced by that cement
そのセメントに置き換えられました
Now many physique cases are made of cement
現在、多くのフィジークケースはセメントで作られています
not only so
それだけではない
Then on the fine coast I want you to see
それから君に見てもらいたい素敵な海岸で
The so-called master of cement that is all cement
全てセメントであるいわゆるマスターオブセメント
something
何か
then we're going to talk about sustainable development
それから持続可能な開発について話します
we can't leave the environment
私たちは環境から離れることはできません
So what I'm wondering now is that
そこで今私が疑問に思っているのは、
How can we change this
これをどう変えるか
the trend of this development
この開発の傾向
Let the reproduction of this fish be able to
この魚の繁殖が可能になりますように
fog as much as possible
できるだけ霧がかかる
Chicken wings can't be completely fogged
手羽先を完全に曇らせることはできません
i wish to say
言いたいです
able to keep some
ある程度は保存できる
Relatively surplus fish breeding
比較的余剰な魚の飼育
like a rainy-breeding environment
雨の多い飼育環境のような
we can talk about sustainability
持続可能性について話すことができます
Otherwise we can only say
そうでなければ、私たちはこう言うことしかできません
From the environment has been pushed down to the laboratory
環境から実験室に押し下げられました
In this way, I am actually the reverse
じゃあ実際は逆なんです
We should develop outside
外で開発すべきだ
So I'm here to listen to you today
それで今日はあなたの話を聞くためにここに来ました
that's why i want to know
だから知りたいのです
That is how we can improve the environment
そうやって環境を改善していきましょう
before being able to
できるようになる前に
To maintain a more sustainable development
より持続可能な発展を維持するために
Thanks
ありがとう
i think this is a big issue
これは大きな問題だと思います
Our land and resources in Taiwan
台湾における私たちの土地と資源
this childcare issue
この育児問題
The first question is more scientific
最初の質問はより科学的です
business issues
ビジネス上の問題
What is a Taiwanese sculpture
台湾彫刻とは
because we all convey
みんなで伝えているから
i think abalone is a cheap fish
アワビはとても安い魚だと思う
But the black abalone has a characteristic
しかし、黒アワビには特徴があります。
Abalone can adapt to fresh water
アワビは淡水にも適応できる
Can also adapt to sea water
海水にも適応できる
you know
ほら
So Taiwan especially has red black abalone
台湾では特に赤黒アワビが有名です
After pre-planting
事前植え付け後
before they bring the fish to market
魚を市場に出す前に
They slowly transform it
彼らはゆっくりとそれを変えていく
form in seawater
海水中で形成される
So it forms in the sea water
つまり海水の中で形成されるのです
it has added value to the product
それは製品に付加価値を与えています
Not only is red turned into a vulture
赤がハゲタカになっただけではありません
Eagles are expensive fish
ワシは高価な魚だ
The second very important thing is
2番目に非常に重要なことは、
it's in the sea
それは海の中にあります
it will remove all kinds of earthy taste
あらゆる種類の土の味を取り除きます
To get rid of organic pests
有機性害虫を駆除するために
The third
第3
fourth fish
4番目の魚
it will become stronger
それは強くなるだろう
because it will reach the sea in pursuit
追いかけて海まで届くから
So then what do we do carving
それで、私たちは何を彫るのですか
You can make Sasimi
刺身も作れます
Why Ubalone Can Be Sasimi
なぜウワロネが刺身になるのか
Because it has been transformed by sea water
海水によって変化したものなので、
so
それで
The head of the family said that this is called Taiwan sculpture
ご当主曰く、これは台湾彫刻というそうです
Let everyone change their image and become this advanced
みんなもイメージチェンジしてこんなに上級者になろう
so we get to this
それでこれに到達します
Especially this restaurant that speaks by mouth
特に口で話すこのレストラン
Its business film must have Taiwanese carvings, right?
ビジネスフィルムには台湾の彫刻が入っているはずですよね？
There are also supermarkets
スーパーマーケットもあります
So where is the Taiwanese sculpture?
では、台湾の彫刻はどこにあるのでしょうか？
This is a product specially developed in Taiwan
台湾で特別に開発された製品です
basically it's a hybrid
基本的にはハイブリッドです
This is the Oreos Mozambica
これがオレオ・モザンビーカです
Not Oreos Nelotica and Oreos
オレオではありません ネロティカとオレオ
Oreochromis
オレオクロミス
Oreos and Nelotica are hybrids
オレオとネロティカはハイブリッドです
Then the purpose of its hybridization is to produce the offspring of this all-bear
そして、その交配の目的は、このすべてのクマの子孫を生み出すことです。
so it's not treated with hormones
だからホルモン治療はしてない
it is hybridized
ハイブリッド化されている
Second your question is very good
次に、あなたの質問はとても良いです
That is to say, the river bank and coast of Taiwan
つまり、台湾の川岸と海岸です。
So for this some protection proposals
したがって、これに対するいくつかの保護提案
Huang Hong and so on are forced by Ba Zhang's phone call.
黄紅らは巴張の電話に迫られる。
The proposal is to combine and assemble
提案は組み合わせて組み立てることです
Well, I think if the Taiwan government is determined
そうですね、台湾政府の決意があればと思います。
The first one is to restore the ecological engineering method
一つ目は、生態工学的手法を復活させることです。
That is to say, your verification case is to
つまり、検証ケースは次のとおりです。
There is no way to fully return to nature
完全に自然に戻る方法はない
It is a quasi-ecological environment to be exposed
疑似生態環境にさらされる
That is to say, no hard cement blocks
つまり、硬いセメントブロックはありません
this way to do this
この方法でこれを行う
step by step i saw
一歩ずつ私は見た
Maybe Mr. Qiu is from Neia
おそらく邱さんはネイア出身だろう
I can't talk nonsense
ナンセンスな話はできない
For example, using stones of different sizes
たとえば、さまざまなサイズの石を使用する
Then it is similar to returning to the state of the river
その後は川の状態に戻るのと同じです
so let it suck
だから吸わせてください
Let these original aquatic organisms fish and shrimp be classed
魚やエビなどのオリジナルの水生生物を分類してみよう
It has four environments that allow it to survive
生き延びるための4つの環境がある
Then this environment is subject to
この環境は次の条件に従うことになります。
The second most important thing is not to pollute
次に大切なのは汚さないこと
man-made pollution factory pollution
人為的汚染 工場汚染
Pollution of this household etc.
この家庭の汚染など
this can't come in
これは入っていけない
I think these two can do
この二人ならできると思う
Of course the third item is the pollution of alpine farmland
もちろん3番目は高山農地の汚染です。
Fertilizer Pesticides wash down
肥料 農薬が洗い流される
If these can be prevented
これらを防ぐことができれば
Taiwan can recover really is
台湾は本当に回復できる
I see Taiwan is beautiful
台湾は美しいですね
To see beautiful Taiwan, no
美しい台湾を見るために、いいえ
Taiwan that has been devastated by this
これで壊滅した台湾
I think this question is very important
この質問はとても重要だと思います
In this way, our biological resources can be sustainable
このようにして、私たちの生物資源は持続可能になります
this development
この展開
Thank you
ありがとう
ok come here
わかった、ここに来て
ask the secretary general
事務局長に聞く
The genetic modification of the fish just mentioned
先ほどの魚の遺伝子組み換え
that technology
その技術
Is this similar to the genetic modification of soybeans
これは大豆の遺伝子組み換えに似ているのでしょうか？
In the same industry, we actually talk about genetic modification
同じ業界では実際に遺伝子組み換えについて話しています
I often have to speak the real meaning from the original English
元の英語から本当の意味を話さなければならないことがよくあります
You know that an organism has about 25,000 to 30,000 genes before
生物には約 25,000 ～ 30,000 個の遺伝子があることが知られています。
In fact, when we talk about transformation, it is as if you said four years a day
実際、変革について話すときは、1 日 4 年と言っているようなものです。
Huang Zi wants to reform, what is reform?
黄子は改革したいのですが、改革とは何ですか？
Maybe keep the basics and replace all the others to be remodeled, right?
おそらく基本はそのままにして、その他はすべて置き換えて改造するのではないかと思います。
In fact, in this translated noun
実際、この翻訳された名詞では、
I think the first one is that there is a considerable gap
1つ目はかなりのギャップがあるということだと思います
We call GMO in English is Genetically Modified Organism
英語ではGMOといいますが、これは遺伝子組み換え生物のことです。
It is based on genetically modified organisms
それは遺伝子組み換え生物に基づいています
It seems that the eyebrows are too thin
眉毛が細すぎる気がする
I want to draw thicker, right?
太めに描きたいですよね？
It's okay to talk about modification, right?
改造について話しても大丈夫ですよね？
this micro
このマイクロ
But our transformation
しかし、私たちの変革
Remodeling is like a revolution, I will replace them all for you
改造は革命のようなもの 全部交換してあげます
actually this
実はこれ
Caused the public in our society to this
私たちの社会の一般大衆にこのようなことを引き起こした
The knowledge of this technology
このテクノロジーの知識
It actually deviates quite a bit
実際はかなりずれます
The first and the second means
1つ目と2つ目の意味は、
We import the genes of foreign aid
外国援助の遺伝子を輸入する
go inside a creature
生き物の中に入っていく
It's all GMO
それはすべてGMOです
Na GMO
那GMO
The history of our human development has existed
私たち人類の発展の歴史は存在します
Human beings have been farming since the beginning
人類が農耕活動を始めてから
For example, your kind is genetically modified.
たとえば、あなたの種族は遺伝子組み換えされています。
That transformation is better than ours
その変革は私たちの変革よりも優れています
with this particular gene
この特定の遺伝子を使って
change to a greater extent
大きく変化する
degree of self-exchange because of a
自己交換の程度
right
右
so we
だから私たちは
If it is to return to us
私たちに戻ってくるのであれば
8,000 years ago to 10,000 years ago
8000年前から1万年前まで
our ancestors
私たちの先祖
You said I ate all the wild ones
野生のものは全部食べたって言ってたね
That's fine
それはいいです
is you to wild to
あなたはそれに夢中ですか？
or wild
または野生
back to the times
時代に戻る
So our concept
そこで私たちのコンセプトは
even scientific
科学的でさえ
i often say
私はよく言います
When discussing or recognizing GMOs
GMOについて議論したり認識したりするとき
have science
科学を持っています
based discussion
ベースのディスカッション
Only then can there be a way to truly understand GMOs
そうして初めて、GMOを真に理解する方法が得られるのです
In particular, I am talking about this life safety assessment
特に、私はこの生命安全評価について話しています。
that's very strict
それはとても厳しいです
Then this piece is linked to this
そうすると、この作品はこれにリンクします
Why does the Council of Agriculture in Taiwan say
台湾農業委員会はなぜこう言うのか
Watch this GMO that is all medicine
すべてが薬であるこのGMOを見てください
it allows us to do
それは私たちにできることです
So why did we come to this viewing instrument
ではなぜ私たちはこの観察装置に辿り着いたのか
We put this technology
私たちはこの技術を投入しました
build a theory like this
このような理論を構築します
But just mentioned that the human population has increased so much
しかし、人間の人口が非常に増加したと先ほど述べました
right
右
We in Taiwan don't seem to feel it
私たち台湾人はそれを感じていないようです
food pressure
食事の圧力
but in the world
しかし世界では
20% of the world's population is still
世界人口の20％は依然として
it is on the verge of activation
活性化寸前です
Then the supply of these foods in the future
そして、将来的にこれらの食品の供給は
I personally feel
個人的に感じているのは
Humans still have technological development
人類はまだテクノロジーの発展を続けています
follow human development
人間の発展に従う
It seems that it goes along with the development
発展に伴ってるようです
When the human population is 9 billion
人類の人口が90億人になったとき
i don't believe that
私はそれを信じません
What we eat every day is not GMO
私たちが毎日食べているものは遺伝子組み換え作物ではありません
Because this feeds nine billion people
これで90億人が養えるから
Thirty-seven years later Thirty-six years later
37年後 36年後
So this is the time to start a rational discussion
だから今こそ合理的な議論を始める時だ
have scientific knowledge
科学的知識を持っている
I personally do it from the point of view
私は個人的な観点からそれをやっています
do this
これを行う
Sometimes our government departments will consider saying
時々、私たちの政府部門はこう言うことを検討するでしょう
This will affect our export
これは輸出に影響します
For example, GM's papaya is actually the world's leading technology
例えば、GMのパパイヤは実は世界最先端の技術だ
But the Agricultural Committee is not the only one
しかし、農業委員会だけではありません。
He said you planted a bad
彼はあなたが悪いものを植え付けたと言った
Foreign countries say I will not buy your papaya from Taiwan
外国は台湾からあなたのパパイヤを買わないと言う
I think you use a specific coin to grow this papaya
このパパイヤを育てるには特定のコインを使用していると思います
You are the guarantee that none of this is leaked
あなたは、この情報が一切漏洩していないことを保証します
It was required by law
それは法律で義務付けられていた
you can't assume say
言うことは想定できない
because when you planted
なぜなら、植えたときに
export can't
輸出できない
People Think You Might Have GMOs
人々はあなたがGMOを持っているかもしれないと考えています
inside
中身
How does this look like getting certified
認定を受けるとどうなるか
This letter of acquisition of citizenship
この市民権取得の手紙
I think this government needs to work on it
この政府はそれに取り組む必要があると思う
Here are some of my personal advances
ここに私の個人的な進歩がいくつかあります
okay, is there anything else
わかりました、他に何かありますか
can ask a question
質問することができます
yes come please
はい、来てください
i want to ask
聞きたいです
That is, the types of fish you just mentioned
つまり、先ほど言った魚の種類です。
all belong to that is to say
すべてが属している、つまり
local small fish
local的小型魚類
Is that because of it
このせいなのか
But the love of the whole ocean
でも海全体の愛は
it has some large return fish
大きな戻り魚がいます
like you mentioned
あなたが言ったように
The tuna factory where Musko and the others make it
ムジコでマグロを作る工場
that's like this
それはこんな感じです
that is why
それが理由です
this biotechnology
このバイオテクノロジー
Is it possible to do the same
同じことは可能ですか
used in the kind of large return oil fish
そういった大型の油戻り魚に使用されます。
Then if from a
次に、
Research unit's point of view
研究ユニットの視点
why only do
なぜそうするだけなのか
That is to say, do not do the above
つまり、上記のようなことはしないでください
OK, what he's talking about is that
OK、彼が言っていることは、
This is the top
これがトップです
upper fish
上層的魚類
like tuna fin fish
マグロのヒレ魚のような
these this
これらはこれ
Costs involving the environment, technology, and investment
環境、技術、投資に関わるコスト
Why tuna?
なぜマグロなのか？
because tuna is in
マグロが入っているので
What they raise is mainly exported to the market in Tokyo, Japan
彼らが育てたものは主に日本の東京の市場に輸出されます
Although tuna can be successfully bred in captivity
マグロは飼育下でも繁殖可能ですが、
But the amount is still not enough
でもまだ量が足りない
so their tuna is
それで彼らのマグロは
Mexico or Australia
メキシコとかオーストラリアとか
they have that
彼らはそれを持っています
Fishing boat, Tuna boat
釣り船・マグロ船
arrive
到着
school of tuna
マグロの群れ
this little school of fish
この小さな魚の群れ
We are talking about little fish
私たちは小さな魚について話しています
This 35kg tuna
こちらは35kgのマグロ
tuna grow big
マグロが大きくなる
they are tuna nets
彼らはマグロ網です
Then
それから
after tuna net
マグロ網後
after shrinking
収縮後
put in
入れます
In this Xiangwang
この翔王では
The Xiangwang in the sea is very active because of the tuna
海の香王はマグロのせいで大活性です
very big
とても大きい
So the tuna from Xiangwang
それで、香王のマグロです。
this diameter
この直径
must be more than 50 meters
50メートル以上ある必要があります
so this
したがって、この
Taiwan because
台湾だから
There are so many in Taiwan, you must be in a place without Taiwan’s waves
台湾にはたくさんあるので、台湾の波のない場所にいるはずです
Only when the impact is too large can there be a solution
影響が大きすぎる場合にのみ解決策がある
So they pass through this way
それで彼らはこの道を通ります
should allow him enough room to return oil
オイルを戻すのに十分な余地を彼に与えるべきだ
To be able to raise a fish like this tuna
こんなマグロのような魚を育てられるなんて
Then the rest is no way this captive breeding
それなら残りはまさかこの飼育下繁殖
Then Taiwan was not what it used to be, and now it still exists
当時の台湾はかつてのようなものではありませんでしたが、今でも台湾は存在しています。
We are raising sea sharks
私たちはウミザメを飼育しています
Sea shark in Penghu in Xiaoliuqiu
澎湖県小琉球のウミザメ
There are industry players who cooperate with the Water City Office
水の都に協力してくれる業界関係者もいる
In fact, it was very successful
実際、それは大成功でした
But here comes the problem, that is, there are two reasons
しかし、ここで問題が発生します。つまり、理由は 2 つあります。
One is a typhoon, it may die and be easily damaged
一つは台風、それは死んで簡単に損傷する可能性があります
the second is
2番目は
some he wants to protect his fish from being stolen
彼は自分の魚を盗まれないよう守りたいと思っている
Some people in Taiwan say that night is the king of tuna
台湾では夜がマグロの王様だという人もいます
where does he go to make water
彼はどこに水を作りに行きますか
He said I was caught at sea
彼は私が海で捕まったと言った
A businessman in Taiwan said this
台湾の実業家はこう言った。
how to say this this
これをどう言うか
There's no way this security can do a good job
このセキュリティがうまく機能するはずがない
So now raise Hailey
だからヘイリーを育ててください
It's only in Penghu, maybe Mintong is relatively simple there.
澎湖だけなので、民通は比較的簡単かもしれません。
There is no such transparent clothing in the sea
海ではあんなに透ける服はない
The Clothes Festival is coming, although there is still
洋服祭りが近づいていますが、まだあります
But Xiao Liuqiu has almost shrunk
しかし、Xiao Liuqiuはほとんど縮小しました
that's a pity
それは残念だ
because haley
なぜならヘイリー
It can grow up to ten kilograms
最大10キロまで成長することもある
Moreover, some politicians can export Japanese
さらに、一部の政治家は日本を輸出できる
There are still, but the quantity is no longer
まだありますが、数量がなくなりました
then as popular as five or six years ago
当時は5、6年前と同じくらい人気がありました
we used to say
私たちはよく言っていた
The Council of Agriculture also hopes to raise Haili from Taiwan
農業委員会も台湾からハイリを育てたいと考えている
Like this, this Norwegian salmon
このように、このノルウェー産サーモンは
Become a fish species representing Taiwan
台湾を代表する魚種となる
Then it slowly evolved into raising grouper
それから徐々にハタの飼育へと進化していきました
So now take the grouper as the
さて、今度はハタを
our main this this
私たちのメインはこれです
a sign is
サインは
But recently the problem is like this
でも最近の悩みはこんな感じ
Xi Jinping slapped his tongue after coming up
習近平は立ち上がった後舌打ちした
So originally Spani was expensive in mainland China
もともとスパニは中国本土では高価だった
You can't treat guests with Spenny now
現在、スペニーでゲストをおもてなしすることはできません
The harmful immigrants not only breed
有害な移民は繁殖するだけではない
Our Spani is live fish transport
私たちのスパニは活魚輸送です
is a live fish that is operated by a boat
船で操業する生きた魚です
Shipping to Tianjin, Qingdao, Shanghai
天津、青島、上海への配送
Previously only created Hong Kong
以前は香港のみを作成していました
Now it is a few ports out of the way
今はいくつかの港から離れたところにあります
But our price is underground
しかし、私たちの価格はアンダーグラウンドです
So you are very lucky
だからあなたたちは本当に幸運です
Spanney is much cheaper now
スパニーは今ではかなり安くなりました
I asked a few days ago
数日前に質問させていただきました
like a normal shift
通常のシフトと同じように
The side price of one kilogram is only 180 yuan
サイド価格は1キログラムでわずか180元です
More than 300 yuan before
以前300多塊
it dropped the general price
一般価格を下げた
so encourage everyone
だからみんなを励ましてください
It's all us Taiwan Spenny
それはすべて私たち台湾スペニーです
Our immigrants will not learn without loss
私たちの移民は損失なくしては学べない
Are there any other questions?
他にご質問はありますか?
I want to ask Secretary-General Wu
呉事務総長に聞きたい
Thank you Secretary-General Wu for giving us a wonderful speech
呉事務総長、素晴らしいスピーチをしていただきありがとうございました
let's applaud and thank him
彼に拍手をして感謝しましょう
thank you all thank you
みんなありがとう、ありがとう